#	id	0
it	O
lies	O
approximately	O
north	O
east	O
of	O
bolesławiec	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
west	O
of	O
the	O
regional	O
capital	O
wrocław	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	1
does	B-CW
anybody	I-CW
really	I-CW
know	I-CW
what	I-CW
time	I-CW
it	I-CW
is?	I-CW
(	O
single	O
version	O
)	O
(	O
lamm	O
)	O
–	O
3	O
:	O
19	O

#	id	2
amrish	B-PER
puri	I-PER
,	O
anupam	B-PER
kher	I-PER
,	O
mukesh	B-PER
khanna	I-PER
,	O
dalip	B-PER
tahil	I-PER
,	O
gulshan	B-PER
grover	I-PER
,	O
dina	B-PER
pathak	I-PER
and	O
jackie	B-PER
shroff	I-PER
are	O
also	O
featured	O
in	O
the	O
movie	O
.	O

#	id	3
wilds	O
himself	O
later	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
coached	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
first	O
saw	O
the	O
victim	O
's	O
body	O
at	O
a	O
certain	O
best	B-CORP
buy	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	4
he	O
scored	O
the	O
first	O
goal	O
of	O
a	O
famous	O
second	O
leg	O
home	O
comeback	O
victory	O
over	O
the	O
great	O
a.c.	B-GRP
milan	I-GRP
of	O
1996	O
(	O
3	O
0	O
)	O
.	O

#	id	6
it	O
is	O
based	O
on	O
pac-man	B-CW
and	O
its	O
derivatives	O
but	O
,	O
like	O
baby	B-CW
pac-man	I-CW
,	O
and	O
pac-man	B-CW
plus	I-CW
,	O
was	O
created	O
without	O
the	O
authorization	O
of	O
namco	B-CORP
.	O

#	id	7
in	O
1919	O
comenius	B-GRP
university	I-GRP
in	I-GRP
bratislava	I-GRP
was	O
founded	O
by	O
an	O
act	O
of	O
parliament	O
in	O
bratislava	B-LOC
,	O
czechoslovakia	B-LOC
,	O
now	O
in	O
slovakia	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	8
before	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
also	O
studied	O
history	O
in	O
tsinghua	B-GRP
university	I-GRP
(	O
in	O
beijing	B-LOC
)	O
during	O
1930	O
1932	O
.	O

#	id	10
steven	B-PER
spielberg	I-PER
first	O
theatrical	O
release	O
,	O
the	B-CW
sugarland	I-CW
express	I-CW
,	O
was	O
set	O
in	O
and	O
partially	O
filmed	O
at	O
the	O
prison	O
.	O

#	id	11
in	O
2009	O
,	O
the	O
company	O
produced	O
watchmen	B-CW
,	O
an	O
adaptation	O
of	O
the	O
dc	B-CORP
comics	I-CORP
limited	O
series	O
watchmen	B-CW
.	O

#	id	12
a	O
nickname	O
given	O
by	O
hobbyist	O
for	O
yokomo	B-CORP

#	id	13
lsh	O
was	O
started	O
from	O
scratch	O
and	O
predates	O
openssh	B-CW
.	O

#	id	14
in	O
the	O
late	O
1970s	O
,	O
he	O
engineered	O
several	O
albums	O
with	O
roy	B-PER
thomas	I-PER
baker	I-PER
,	O
eventually	O
leaving	O
in	O
the	O
1980s	O
to	O
become	O
a	O
full	O
time	O
producer	O
.	O

#	id	16
elon	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
jerusalem	B-LOC
in	O
1950	O
.	O

#	id	17
brev	O
til	O
et	O
menneske	O
on	O
gyldendal	B-CORP
norsk	I-CORP
forlag	I-CORP
in	O
1980	O
.	O

#	id	18
he	O
received	O
treatments	O
for	O
his	O
recurring	O
stomach	O
upsets	O
in	O
vichy	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	19
the	O
project	O
was	O
by	O
giovanni	B-PER
battista	I-PER
foggini	I-PER
and	O
the	O
church	O
was	O
completed	O
a	O
few	O
years	O
later	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
for	O
worship	O
until	O
1714	O
.	O

#	id	22
carlyle	B-PER
mitchell	I-PER
suffered	O
an	O
injury	O
which	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
sit	O
out	O
for	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
season	O
.	O

#	id	23
the	O
center	O
developed	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
varieties	O
of	O
glycine	B-PROD
max	I-PROD
for	O
use	O
in	O
different	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
early	O
maturing	O
varieties	O
yielded	O
over	O
1,200	O
kg	O
/	O
ha	O
of	O
soybeans	O
.	O

#	id	24
lanterns	O
may	O
also	O
be	O
used	O
for	O
signaling	O
,	O
as	O
flashlight	B-PROD
,	O
or	O
as	O
general	O
light	O
sources	O
outdoors	O
.	O

#	id	25
tokitaka	O
was	O
a	O
father	O
in	O
law	O
of	O
shimazu	B-PER
yoshihisa	I-PER
.	O

#	id	26
they	O
were	O
extensively	O
refurbished	O
between	O
1989	O
and	O
1992	O
by	O
eastleigh	B-CORP
works	I-CORP
,	O
for	O
use	O
on	O
services	O
on	O
the	O
isle	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
wight	I-LOC
island	B-LOC
line,	I-LOC
isle	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
wight	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	27
it	O
is	O
known	O
from	O
a	O
single	O
specimen	O
found	O
off	O
the	O
coast	O
of	O
new	B-LOC
zealand	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	29
you	B-CW
are	I-CW
my	I-CW
sunshine	I-CW
(	O
with	O
sheryl	B-PER
crow	I-PER
&	O
jon	B-PER
brion	I-PER
)	O
(	O
3	O
:	O
35	O
)	O

#	id	30
the	O
classic	O
tree	O
paint	O
is	O
black	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
is	O
based	O
on	O
an	O
asphalt	B-PROD
emulsion	O
.	O

#	id	31
alaungpaya	O
sought	O
an	O
alliance	O
with	O
the	O
east	B-CORP
india	I-CORP
company	I-CORP
and	O
also	O
sought	O
out	O
more	O
arms	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
alliance	O
or	O
arms	O
materialized	O
.	O

#	id	32
zara	B-CORP
also	O
opened	O
a	O
location	O
in	O
the	O
mall	O
in	O
2016	O
.	O

#	id	33
each	O
week	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
segments	O
were	O
presented	O
on	O
topics	O
such	O
as	O
fishing	O
,	O
boating	O
and	O
marine	O
lifestyle	O
with	O
the	O
series	O
shot	O
mostly	O
in	O
australia	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	34
the	O
franchise	O
was	O
put	O
up	O
for	O
sale	O
after	O
the	O
1993	O
–	O
94	O
season	O
and	O
an	O
ownership	O
group	O
from	O
mexico	B-LOC
city	I-LOC
purchased	O
the	O
franchise	O
over	O
two	O
other	O
bids	O
.	O

#	id	35
it	O
was	O
named	O
best	O
sports	O
film	O
of	O
all	O
time	O
by	O
usa	B-GRP
today	I-GRP
and	O
by	O
espn	B-CORP
expert	O
panel	O
and	O
website	O
users	O
.	O

#	id	36
fairly	O
serious	O
in	O
content	O
with	O
a	O
focus	O
on	O
radical	O
organizing	O
issues	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
loosely	O
aligned	O
with	O
the	O
students	B-GRP
for	I-GRP
a	I-GRP
democratic	I-GRP
society	I-GRP
movement	O
.	O

#	id	38
fourth	O
round	O
lost	O
to	O
marion	B-PER
bartoli	I-PER
[	O
11	O
]	O

#	id	39
the	B-CW
little	I-CW
prince	I-CW
(	O
november	O
2015	O
)	O
–	O
girl	O

#	id	40
fly-whisk	B-PROD
,	O
made	O
of	O
yak	O
tail	O
(	O
,	O
thamyi	O
yat	O
)	O

#	id	41
his	O
work	O
has	O
been	O
shown	O
in	O
exhibitions	O
at	O
museums	O
such	O
as	O
the	O
jordan	B-LOC
national	I-LOC
gallery	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
fine	I-LOC
arts	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	42
married	O
1894	O
(	O
6	O
august	O
)	O
,	O
grand	B-PER
duchess	I-PER
xenia	I-PER
alexandrovna	I-PER
of	I-PER
russia	I-PER
(	O
1875	O
–	O
1960	O
)	O
;	O
1	O
daughter	O
,	O
6	O
sons	O
.	O

#	id	43
since	O
2008	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
senior	O
vice	O
president	O
of	O
disney	B-CORP
television	I-CORP
animation	I-CORP
(	O
owned	O
by	O
the	B-GRP
walt	I-GRP
disney	I-GRP
company	I-GRP
)	O
.	O

#	id	44
it	O
is	O
affiliated	O
and	O
accredited	O
to	O
university	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
north	I-GRP
bengal	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	46
the	O
recently	O
excavated	O
terracotta	B-PROD
system	O
is	O
located	O
along	O
the	O
eastern	O
ground	O
entrance	O
and	O
is	O
well	O
preserved	O
.	O

#	id	47
it	O
was	O
based	O
on	O
theodore	B-PER
dreiser	I-PER
1925	O
novel	O
an	B-CW
american	I-CW
tragedy	I-CW
.	O

#	id	48
a	O
new	O
acquisition	O
in	O
1956	O
was	O
singer	B-CORP
motors	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	49
the	O
prize	O
was	O
instead	O
awarded	O
to	O
the	O
united	B-LOC
kingdom	I-LOC
black	B-CW
comedy	I-CW
if....	B-CW
.	O

#	id	50
olympic	O
coach	O
(	O
kristy	B-PER
swanson	I-PER
)	O
trains	O
teen	O
diver	O
who	O
's	O
afraid	O
of	O
heights	O
.	O

#	id	52
an	O
example	O
of	O
this	O
model	O
can	O
be	O
command-line	B-CW
interface	I-CW
(	O
e.g.	O
copy	O
,	O
here	O
the	O
action	O
copy	O
is	O
specified	O
prior	O
to	O
the	O
object	O
file	O
)	O
.	O

#	id	53
the	O
first	O
elder	O
they	O
present	O
their	O
argument	O
to	O
is	O
an	O
old	O
withering	O
apricot	B-PROD
tree	O
.	O

#	id	55
thomas	B-PER
scrubb	I-PER
(	O
born	O
1991	O
)	O
,	O
professional	O
basketball	O
player	O

#	id	56
on	O
telegram	B-CW
,	O
a	O
white	O
supremacist	O
channel	O
encouraged	O
members	O
to	O
distribute	O
the	O
propaganda	O
.	O

#	id	57
sephardim	O
do	O
not	O
put	O
on	O
tefillin	B-PROD
during	O
ḥol	O
ha	O
mo	O
ed	O
(	O
the	O
middle	O
days	O
of	O
festivals	O
)	O
.	O

#	id	58
upon	O
publication	O
a	O
review	O
by	O
the	O
poet	O
kenneth	B-PER
rexroth	I-PER
appeared	O
in	O
the	B-GRP
new	I-GRP
york	I-GRP
times	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	59
ayen	O
is	O
located	O
some	O
20	O
km	O
north	O
west	O
of	O
brive-la-gaillarde	B-LOC
and	O
7	O
km	O
west	O
of	O
objat	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	60
emi	B-CORP
,	O
a	O
music	O
and	O
electronics	O
group	O
of	O
companies	O

#	id	62
she	O
started	O
playing	O
squash	O
in	O
england	B-LOC
at	O
age	O
12	O
.	O

#	id	63
he	O
also	O
directed	O
the	O
comedy	O
big	B-CW
trouble	I-CW
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
most	O
successful	O
film	O
sequel	O
to	O
that	O
point	O
,	O
men	B-CW
in	I-CW
black	I-CW
ii	I-CW
.	O

#	id	64
ricci	O
tried	O
an	O
escape	O
manoeuver	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
thwarted	O
by	O
a	O
mini	B-PROD
casually	O
parked	O
at	O
the	O
crossroad	O
.	O

#	id	65
pelit	B-CW
gave	O
the	O
game	O
90	O
out	O
of	O
100	O
.	O

#	id	66
file	O
:	O
mf	O
ærøxpressen	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
jpg	O
|	O
m	O
/	O
f	O
ærøxpressen	O
,	O
2019	O
marstal	B-LOC
rudkøbing	B-LOC

#	id	67
this	O
bitter	O
,	O
bold	O
taste	O
herbal	O
liqueur	O
is	O
mainly	O
consumed	O
as	O
an	O
apéritif	B-PROD
before	O
meals	O
or	O
a	O
digestif	B-PROD
after	O
meals	O
.	O

#	id	68
curitiba	O
was	O
recently	O
recommended	O
by	O
unesco	B-GRP
as	O
a	O
model	O
for	O
the	O
reconstruction	O
of	O
the	O
cities	O
of	O
afghanistan	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	70
sandbox	O
and	O
delivery	O
pipe	O
of	O
a	O
db	B-PROD
class	I-PROD
103	I-PROD

#	id	71
the	O
incumbent	O
local	O
exchange	O
carrier	O
for	O
the	O
area	O
codes	O
is	O
bell	B-CORP
mts	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	72
he	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
carolina	B-GRP
panthers	I-GRP
and	O
pittsburgh	B-GRP
steelers	I-GRP
in	O
the	O
national	B-CORP
football	I-CORP
league	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	73
at	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
1877	O
a	O
tram	B-PROD
arrived	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
centre	O
.	O

#	id	74
portions	O
of	O
the	O
report	O
were	O
copied	O
,	O
without	O
attribution	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
2011	O
article	O
in	O
mother	B-CW
jones	I-CW
.	O

#	id	75
in	O
1996	O
he	O
studied	O
for	O
a	O
year	O
at	O
glasgow	B-GRP
school	I-GRP
of	I-GRP
art	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	78
they	O
also	O
mentioned	O
that	O
this	O
would	O
benefit	O
france	B-LOC
influence	O
in	O
the	O
region	O
.	O

#	id	79
his	O
son	O
,	O
jeremy	B-PER
duchesne	I-PER
,	O
is	O
a	O
former	O
goaltending	O
prospect	O
for	O
the	O
philadelphia	B-GRP
flyers	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	81
the	O
deluxe	O
limited	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
album	O
includes	O
a	O
bonus	O
track	O
and	O
a	O
bonus	O
dvd	B-PROD
containing	O
a	O
look	O
behind	O
the	O
scenes	O
and	O
special	O
bonus	O
footage	O
.	O

#	id	82
bennett	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
nicknamed	O
after	O
the	O
charlie	B-PER
chaplin	I-PER
since	O
his	O
youth	O
.	O

#	id	83
small	O
fish	O
and	O
shrimp	B-PROD
(	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
fish	O
trade	O
;	O
most	O
people	O
say	O
hiki	O
instead	O
)	O

#	id	85
he	O
then	O
moved	O
onto	O
london	B-LOC
lbc	B-CORP
programming	O
an	O
all	O
talk	O
and	O
phone	O
in	O
format	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
become	O
so	O
familiar	O
.	O

#	id	86
rock	B-CW
monster	I-CW
(	O
director	O
/	O
writer	O
)	O

#	id	88
1989	O
mission:	B-CW
impossible	I-CW
(	O
tv	O
series	O
)	O
1	O
episode	O

#	id	89
amy	B-PER
aquino	I-PER
,	O
film	O
and	O
television	O
actress	O

#	id	90
for	O
example	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
potential	O
difference	O
across	O
a	O
capacitor	B-PROD
is	O
halved	O
,	O
the	O
quantity	O
of	O
charge	O
stored	O
by	O
that	O
capacitor	O
will	O
also	O
be	O
halved	O
.	O

#	id	91
after	O
a	O
series	O
of	O
civil	O
jobs	O
he	O
settled	O
in	O
kristiansand	B-LOC
in	O
1892	O
as	O
a	O
postmaster	O
.	O

#	id	92
one	O
bad	O
characteristic	O
of	O
httrack	B-CW
is	O
that	O
it	O
renames	O
files	O
during	O
the	O
archiving	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
original	O
structure	O
of	O
the	O
website	O
is	O
lost	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
file	O
names	O
.	O

#	id	93
enstrom	B-CORP
helicopter	I-CORP
corporation	I-CORP
,	O
makers	O
of	O
several	O
small	O
helicopter	O
designs	O

#	id	94
calkins	O
research	O
was	O
cited	O
by	O
sigmund	B-PER
freud	I-PER
when	O
he	O
created	O
his	O
conception	O
of	O
the	O
dream	O
.	O

#	id	95
february	O
17	O
–	O
shōichirō	B-PER
toyoda	I-PER
,	O
business	O
executive	O

#	id	96
ten	O
years	O
later	O
fruehauf	B-CORP
trailer	I-CORP
corporation	I-CORP
experimented	O
with	O
tractor	O
trailers	O
.	O

#	id	97
the	B-CW
middle	I-CW
(	O
set	O
in	O
fictional	O
town	O
of	O
orson	O
)	O

#	id	98
the	O
book	O
also	O
became	O
the	O
basis	O
for	O
a	O
weekly	O
television	O
series	O
on	O
nbc	B-CORP
that	O
ran	O
for	O
13	O
weeks	O
in	O
1978	O
.	O

#	id	100
microsoft	B-CW
windows	I-CW
1.03	O
,	O
little	O
known	O
and	O
little	O
used	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
run	O
in	O
this	O
environment	O
.	O

#	id	102
he	O
earned	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
nine	O
caps	O
for	O
ireland	B-GRP
national	I-GRP
under-20	I-GRP
rugby	I-GRP
union	I-GRP
team	I-GRP
,	O
scoring	O
a	O
single	O
try	O
.	O

#	id	103
john	B-PER
blacking	I-PER
was	O
another	O
ethnomusicologist	O
who	O
sought	O
to	O
create	O
an	O
ethnomusicological	O
parallel	O
to	O
linguistic	O
models	O
of	O
analysis	O
.	O

#	id	104
the	O
powertrain	B-PROD
delivers	O
enough	O
torque	O
to	O
the	O
wheel	O
to	O
overcome	O
stationary	O
forces	O
,	O
resulting	O
in	O
the	O
vehicle	O
moving	O
forwards	O
or	O
backwards	O
.	O

#	id	106
the	O
show	O
brought	O
the	O
band	O
back	O
and	O
got	O
them	O
attention	O
from	O
record	O
labels	O
like	O
century	B-CORP
media	I-CORP
records	I-CORP
and	O
victory	B-CORP
records	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	107
he	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
principality	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
terebovlia	I-LOC
from	O
1092	O
.	O

#	id	108
[	O
there	O
are	O
]	O
three	O
terraced	O
pools	O
made	O
of	O
concrete	O
and	O
covered	O
with	O
white	O
mosaic	B-PROD
glass	O
tiles	O
.	O

#	id	109
mcclurg	O
's	O
lifelong	O
friendship	O
with	O
thomas	B-PER
jefferson	I-PER
dated	O
from	O
their	O
school	O
days	O
.	O

#	id	110
the	O
first	O
chapel	B-LOC
was	O
built	O
in	O
1716	O
.	O

#	id	112
a	O
year	O
later	O
he	O
joined	O
the	O
newly	O
formed	O
london	B-GRP
broncos	I-GRP
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
key	O
member	O
of	O
their	O
inaugural	O
squad	O
.	O

#	id	113
nicolás	B-PER
almagro	I-PER
was	O
the	O
defending	O
champion	O
but	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
final	O
,	O
7	O
–	O
6	O
(	O
7	O
–	O
5	O
)	O
,	O
6	O
–	O
4	O
,	O
to	O
jerzy	B-PER
janowicz	I-PER
.	O

#	id	117
the	O
last	O
model	O
was	O
the	O
fiat	B-PROD
ritmo	I-PROD
and	O
the	O
company	O
closed	O
its	O
doors	O
in	O
1978	O
.	O

#	id	118
mudlark	O
,	O
a	O
model	O
of	O
penton	B-CORP
off	O
road	O
motorcycle	O

#	id	120
m.u.d.	B-CW
tv	I-CW
,	O
another	O
television	O
station	O
simulation	O
game	O

#	id	121
huan	B-PER
xuan	I-PER
sacks	O
jiankang	B-LOC
and	O
sun	B-PER
en	I-PER
dies	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
lieutenant	O
lu	B-PER
xun	I-PER
takes	O
over	O
}	O

#	id	122
this	O
diversion	O
from	O
traditional	O
yacht	O
structure	O
led	O
to	O
disagreements	O
with	O
lloyd's	B-CORP
register	I-CORP
assessors	O
for	O
insurance	O
purposes	O
.	O

#	id	123
it	O
sits	O
on	O
the	O
river	B-LOC
walkham	I-LOC
,	O
a	O
fishing	O
river	O
famous	O
for	O
its	O
salmon	O
.	O

#	id	124
it	O
was	O
discovered	O
in	O
1958	O
and	O
developed	O
by	O
omv	B-CORP
petrom	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	125
the	O
variant	O
was	O
named	O
after	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
youngstown	B-LOC
where	O
the	O
variant	O
was	O
invented	O
.	O

#	id	126
sergi	B-PER
pàmies	I-PER
(	O
born	O
1960	O
)	O
,	O
writer	O
,	O
translator	O
,	O
journalist	O

#	id	127
mike	B-PER
love	I-PER
–	O
lead	O
,	O
harmony	O
and	O
backing	O
vocals	O

#	id	128
renumbered	O
802	O
and	O
leased	O
to	O
v/line	B-CORP
1998	O
–	O
1999	O
.	O

#	id	129
alice	B-GRP
in	I-GRP
chains	I-GRP
(	O
first	O
studio	O
album	O
since	O
1995	O
,	O
and	O
first	O
release	O
with	O
william	B-PER
duvall	I-PER
on	O
vocals	O
)	O

#	id	130
the	O
wort	O
is	O
moved	O
into	O
a	O
large	O
tank	O
known	O
as	O
a	O
copper	O
or	O
kettle	B-PROD
where	O
it	O
is	O
boiled	O
with	O
hops	B-PROD
and	O
sometimes	O
other	O
ingredients	O
such	O
as	O
herbs	O
or	O
sugars	O
.	O

#	id	131
in	O
other	O
press	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
were	O
named	O
one	O
of	O
television	O
's	O
top	O
power	O
couples	O
by	O
tv	B-CW
guide	I-CW
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
supercouples	O
by	O
entertainment	B-CW
weekly	I-CW
.	O

#	id	132
white	O
was	O
cast	O
on	O
the	O
television	O
series	O
survivor:	B-CW
samoa	I-CW
,	O
the	O
19th	O
season	O
of	O
the	O
united	B-LOC
states	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
america	I-LOC
version	O
of	O
survivor	B-CW
.	O

#	id	133
the	O
pal	B-CORP
video	O
signal	O
is	O
slightly	O
different	O
in	O
that	O
it	O
swings	O
from	O
300	O
mv	O
to	O
+	O
700	O
mv	O
,	O
instead	O
.	O

#	id	134
he	O
was	O
the	O
brother	O
of	O
the	O
dramatist	O
thomas	B-PER
killigrew	I-PER
and	O
of	O
elizabeth	B-PER
killigrew,	I-PER
viscountess	I-PER
shannon	I-PER
,	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
future	O
charles	B-PER
ii	I-PER
of	I-PER
england	I-PER
.	O

#	id	135
comprising	O
several	O
municipalities	O
and	O
urban	O
centres	O
,	O
the	O
subregion	O
's	O
capital	O
is	O
setúbal	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
includes	O
several	O
cities	O
including	O
almada	B-LOC
and	O
setúbal	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	136
with	O
background	O
in	O
anthropology	O
,	O
economics	O
,	O
and	O
statistics	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
anthropology	O
professor	O
franz	B-PER
boas	I-PER
.	O

#	id	137
during	O
the	O
events	O
of	O
avengers	B-CW
vs.	I-CW
x-men	I-CW
,	O
she	O
starts	O
a	O
sentimental	O
relationship	O
with	O
him	O
.	O

#	id	138
a	O
genre	O
that	O
emerged	O
in	O
the	O
1930s	O
to	O
consistent	O
popular	O
acclaim	O
was	O
the	O
musical	O
comedy	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
master	O
of	O
that	O
form	O
was	O
grigori	B-PER
aleksandrov	I-PER
(	O
1903	O
–	O
1984	O
)	O
.	O

#	id	139
at	O
least	O
five	O
of	O
his	O
branch	O
libraries	O
have	O
survived	O
and	O
are	O
designated	O
as	O
listed	B-LOC
building	I-LOC
in	I-LOC
the	I-LOC
united	I-LOC
kingdom	I-LOC
by	O
english	B-GRP
heritage	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	140
prince	B-PER
henry,	I-PER
duke	I-PER
of	I-PER
gloucester	I-PER
and	O
princess	B-PER
alice,	I-PER
duchess	I-PER
of	I-PER
gloucester	I-PER
,	O
the	O
bride	O
's	O
paternal	O
uncle	O
and	O
aunt	O

#	id	141
the	O
eastern	O
area	O
is	O
urban	O
and	O
integrated	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
with	O
industrial	O
zones	O
(	O
kellogg	B-CORP
company	I-CORP
)	O
and	O
military	O
facilities	O
.	O

#	id	142
all	O
compositions	O
by	O
richard	B-PER
m.	I-PER
sherman	I-PER
and	O
robert	B-PER
b.	I-PER
sherman	I-PER

#	id	146
john	O
begins	O
construction	O
of	O
a	O
royal	O
navy	B-GRP
.	O

#	id	147
her	O
godparent	B-PER
was	O
john	B-PER
forster	I-PER
,	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
friend	O
and	O
later	O
biographer	O
.	O

#	id	148
the	O
website	O
also	O
offers	O
other	O
on	O
line	O
companies	O
the	O
ability	O
to	O
provide	O
their	O
customers	O
with	O
a	O
co	O
branded	O
or	O
white-label	B-PROD
product	I-PROD
comparison	O
service	O
.	O

#	id	149
in	O
1995	O
,	O
he	O
starred	O
in	O
an	O
episode	O
of	O
the	B-CW
x-files	I-CW
.	O

#	id	150
depositions	O
usually	O
take	O
place	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
reporter	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
law	B-CORP
firm	I-CORP
involved	O
in	O
a	O
case	O
.	O

#	id	152
dagmar	B-PER
krause	I-PER
(	O
credited	O
as	O
dagmar	O
)	O
–	O
voice	O
,	O
rudolph	B-CORP
wurlitzer	I-CORP
company	I-CORP
(	O
in	O
the	O
sickbay	O
)	O

#	id	153
her	O
writing	O
appears	O
in	O
gq	B-CW
,	O
vogue	B-CW
and	O
the	B-GRP
guardian	I-GRP
and	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
regular	O
arts	O
critic	O
in	O
print	O
,	O
on	O
television	O
and	O
on	O
radio	O
.	O

#	id	154
during	O
the	O
programme	O
he	O
met	O
individuals	O
such	O
as	O
john	B-PER
godber	I-PER
,	O
fred	B-PER
trueman	I-PER
and	O
kathy	B-PER
staff	I-PER
.	O

#	id	155
the	O
new	B-CW
testament	I-CW
references	O
are	O
and	O
.	O

#	id	157
they	O
drank	O
chocolate	O
with	O
corn	O
puree	O
,	O
or	O
masa	B-PROD
.	O

#	id	159
adimali	O
is	O
a	O
relatively	O
new	O
town	O
located	O
between	O
kochi	B-LOC
and	O
munnar	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	160
in	O
1934	O
he	O
directed	O
his	O
first	O
picture	O
,	O
the	B-CW
silver	I-CW
streak	I-CW
,	O
which	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
top	O
money	O
makers	O
for	O
rko	B-GRP
pictures	I-GRP
that	O
year	O
.	O

#	id	161
he	O
played	O
on	O
the	O
hit	O
love	B-CW
is	I-CW
strange	I-CW
by	O
mickey	B-CORP
&	I-CORP
sylvia	I-CORP
and	O
was	O
music	O
director	O
for	O
the	B-GRP
ink	I-GRP
spots	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	162
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
season	O
,	O
the	O
top	O
four	O
teams	O
enter	O
a	O
playoff	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
plays	O
in	O
the	O
european	B-GRP
hockey	I-GRP
league	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	163
(	O
it	O
previously	O
had	O
been	O
available	O
on	O
dec	B-PROD
alpha	I-PROD
under	O
tru64	B-CW
unix	I-CW
until	O
usage	O
of	O
that	O
platform	O
generally	O
died	O
out	O
.	O
)	O

#	id	164
its	O
wood	O
is	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
red	O
dye	B-PROD
.	O

#	id	165
scheifele	O
played	O
on	O
a	O
line	O
with	O
tanner	B-PER
pearson	I-PER
and	O
each	O
set	O
each	O
other	O
up	O
for	O
goals	O
to	O
win	O
the	O
bronze	O
medal	O
.	O

#	id	166
this	O
allows	O
the	O
public	O
to	O
understand	O
how	O
the	O
volunteers	O
are	O
organized	O
in	O
their	O
local	O
community	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
used	O
as	O
a	O
public	B-PROD
relations	I-PROD
tool	O
.	O

#	id	167
he	O
launched	O
both	O
games	O
in	O
1985	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
year	O
he	O
debuted	O
u.s.a.a.f.	B-CW
-	I-CW
united	I-CW
states	I-CW
army	I-CW
air	I-CW
force	I-CW
.	O

#	id	169
the	O
ground	O
surface	O
quickly	O
turns	O
to	O
a	O
consistency	O
of	O
cream	B-PROD
cheese	I-PROD
and	O
on	O
the	O
coast	O
troop	O
movements	O
were	O
confined	O
to	O
roads	O
,	O
except	O
during	O
frosts	O
.	O

#	id	170
although	O
resilient	O
in	O
many	O
soil	O
types	O
,	O
this	O
species	O
grows	O
best	O
in	O
sandy	O
or	O
loam	B-PROD
soils	O
.	O

#	id	171
due	O
to	O
the	O
limited	O
release	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
chart	O
on	O
oricon	B-CORP
.	O

#	id	172
nathan	B-PER
coe	I-PER
personal	O
life	O

#	id	173
the	O
book	B-CW
cover	I-CW
is	O
made	O
using	O
three	O
separate	O
pieces	O
:	O
front	O
cover	O
,	O
back	O
cover	O
,	O
and	O
spine	O
piece	O
.	O

#	id	174
with	O
his	O
work	O
he	O
has	O
repeatedly	O
asked	O
questions	O
contemporary	B-CW
art	I-CW
,	O
in	O
particular	O
on	O
structure	O
and	O
order	O
,	O
shape	O
and	O
space	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
line	O
and	O
color	O
.	O

#	id	176
kim	B-PER
ng	I-PER
(	O
a.b.	O
1990	O
)	O
–	O
senior	O
vice	O
president	O
of	O
operations	O
with	O
major	B-CORP
league	I-CORP
baseball	I-CORP
,	O
former	O
assistant	O
general	O
manager	O
of	O
los	B-GRP
angeles	I-GRP
dodgers	I-GRP

#	id	177
1992	O
(	O
march	O
)	O
–	O
north	O
face	O
of	O
the	O
eiger	B-LOC

#	id	178
american	O
weekly	O
radio	O
show	O
wait	B-CW
wait...	I-CW
don't	I-CW
tell	I-CW
me!	I-CW
was	O
started	O
in	O
1998	O
on	O
public	O
radio	O
network	O
npr	B-CORP
.	O

#	id	180
the	O
production	O
was	O
directed	O
by	O
john	B-PER
gielgud	I-PER
.	O

#	id	181
jacob	O
is	O
the	O
author	O
of	O
the	O
book	B-CW
of	I-CW
jacob	I-CW
in	O
the	O
book	B-CW
of	I-CW
mormon	I-CW
.	O

#	id	182
they	O
use	O
a	O
school	B-PROD
bus	I-PROD
to	O
travel	O
to	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
campus	O
.	O

#	id	183
this	O
match	O
was	O
later	O
shown	O
on	O
wcw	B-CW
saturday	I-CW
night	I-CW
.	O

#	id	184
his	O
son	O
kisshomaru	B-PER
ueshiba	I-PER
was	O
born	O
in	O
the	O
summer	O
of	O
1921	O
.	O

#	id	185
prior	O
to	O
her	O
political	O
career	O
she	O
worked	O
in	O
investment	O
banking	O
for	O
jpmorgan	B-CORP
chase	I-CORP
and	O
bank	B-CORP
of	I-CORP
america	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	186
codemasters	B-CORP
released	O
rise	B-CW
of	I-CW
the	I-CW
argonauts	I-CW
,	O
an	O
action	B-CW
game	I-CW
role-playing	B-CW
video	I-CW
game	I-CW
developed	O
by	O
liquid	B-CORP
entertainment	I-CORP
,	O
in	O
2008	O
.	O

#	id	187
donald	B-PER
trump	I-PER
,	O
portrayed	O
as	O
entirely	O
orange	O
,	O
aside	O
from	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
with	O
tiny	O
hands	O
and	O
a	O
toilet	O
seat	O
and	O
lid	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
hairstyle	O
.	O

#	id	188
these	O
roles	O
required	O
him	O
to	O
work	O
closely	O
with	O
dynamit	B-CORP
nobel	I-CORP
and	O
as	O
such	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
that	O
company	O
's	O
supervisory	O
board	O
from	O
1936	O
until	O
1945	O
.	O

#	id	189
gene	B-PER
kelly	I-PER
had	O
a	O
special	O
affection	O
for	O
her	O
and	O
included	O
her	O
in	O
each	O
of	O
his	O
films	O
following	O
her	O
role	O
in	O
an	B-CW
american	I-CW
in	I-CW
paris	I-CW
.	O

#	id	191
crickets	B-CW
sing	I-CW
for	I-CW
anamaria	I-CW
(	O
marcos	B-PER
valle	I-PER
)	O
1	O
:	O
36	O

#	id	192
wheeler	O
had	O
a	O
united	B-CORP
states	I-CORP
postal	I-CORP
service	I-CORP
at	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
no	O
longer	O
exists	O
.	O

#	id	193
in	O
1928	O
al	O
haffar	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
nationalist	O
leaders	O
,	O
founded	O
the	O
national	B-GRP
bloc	I-GRP
in	O
beirut	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	194
he	O
died	O
in	O
1986	O
in	O
southampton	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	195
it	O
is	O
found	O
in	O
ecuador	B-LOC
and	O
peru	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	196
anthony	B-PER
recker	I-PER
,	O
former	O
professional	O
baseball	O
player	O
,	O
atlanta	B-GRP
braves	I-GRP
,	O
chicago	B-GRP
cubs	I-GRP
,	O
new	B-GRP
york	I-GRP
mets	I-GRP
and	O
oakland	B-GRP
athletics	I-GRP

#	id	198
large	O
areas	O
were	O
cleared	O
to	O
grow	O
more	O
sugarcane	B-PROD
,	O
and	O
so	O
few	O
trees	O
remained	O
that	O
timber	O
had	O
to	O
be	O
imported	O
.	O

#	id	199
commercial	O
cultivar	B-PROD
mostly	O
only	O
grow	O
to	O
about	O
5	O
m	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
frequently	O
trimmed	O
as	O
low	O
as	O
2	O
m	O
to	O
facilitate	O
harvesting	O
.	O

#	id	200
discusses	O
some	O
pitfalls	O
in	O
interpreting	O
and	O
translating	O
the	O
new	B-CW
testament	I-CW
.	O

#	id	201
kaspar	O
was	O
portrayed	O
by	O
fabienne	B-PER
dali	I-PER
in	O
the	O
1968	O
film	O
mayerling	B-CW
.	O

#	id	202
malik	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
lahore	B-LOC
in	O
1997	O
to	O
a	O
family	O
of	O
three	O
siblings	O
.	O

#	id	203
joey	B-PER
logano	I-PER
was	O
forced	O
to	O
drop	O
to	O
the	O
tail	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
line	O
for	O
an	O
uncontrolled	O
tire	O
.	O

#	id	204
zbigniew	B-PER
preisner	I-PER
–	O
blue	B-CW
(	O
trois	O
couleurs	O
:	O
bleu	O
)	O
,	O
the	B-CW
secret	I-CW
garden	I-CW
and	O
olivier	B-CW

#	id	207
it	O
is	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
production	O
of	O
several	O
local	O
(	O
mainly	O
white	O
)	O
wine	B-PROD
.	O

#	id	209
landslide	B-CW
by	O
fleetwood	B-GRP
mac	I-GRP
(	O
highest	O
number	O
of	O
votes	O
)	O

#	id	213
he	O
was	O
consultant	O
to	O
the	O
royal	B-GRP
highland	I-GRP
and	I-GRP
agricultural	I-GRP
society	I-GRP
of	I-GRP
scotland	I-GRP
from	O
1900	O
to	O
1930	O
.	O

#	id	214
henry	B-PER
purcell	I-PER
and	O
george	B-PER
frideric	I-PER
handel	I-PER
both	O
wrote	O
pieces	O
for	O
it	O
.	O

#	id	215
in	O
1917	O
he	O
earned	O
his	O
medical	O
degree	O
and	O
moved	O
to	O
the	O
dominican	B-LOC
republic	I-LOC
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
as	O
the	O
medical	O
physician	O
at	O
a	O
sugar	O
plantation	O
.	O

#	id	216
a	O
list	O
of	O
cities	O
,	O
towns	O
and	O
villages	O
in	O
south	B-LOC
khorasan	I-LOC
province	I-LOC
of	O
eastern	O
iran	B-LOC
:	O

#	id	218
he	O
made	O
his	O
debut	O
2	O
weeks	O
later	O
,	O
coming	O
on	O
as	O
a	O
substitute	O
for	O
leandro	B-PER
trossard	I-PER
in	O
a	O
2	O
–	O
1	O
away	O
defeat	O
against	O
tottenham	B-GRP
hotspur	I-GRP
f.c.	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	219
hart	O
lent	O
his	O
nickname	O
to	O
the	O
calgary	B-GRP
hitmen	I-GRP
of	O
the	O
western	B-GRP
hockey	I-GRP
league	I-GRP
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
founder	O
and	O
part	O
owner	O
.	O

#	id	220
npr	B-CORP
called	O
that	O
event	O
the	O
gullah	O
reunion	O
.	O

#	id	222
deguara	O
was	O
then	O
signed	O
by	O
newly	O
formed	O
national	B-GRP
basketball	I-GRP
league	I-GRP
of	I-GRP
canada	I-GRP
side	O
niagara	B-GRP
river	I-GRP
lions	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	223
orbeliani	O
died	O
in	O
tbilisi	B-LOC
in	O
1796	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
interred	O
at	O
tbilisi	B-LOC
sioni	I-LOC
cathedral	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	225
say	B-CW
my	I-CW
name	I-CW
destiny's	B-GRP
child	I-GRP
(	O
mistakenly	O
credited	O
as	O
say	O
your	O
name	O
)	O

#	id	226
first	O
produced	O
and	O
published	O
for	O
the	O
nintendo	B-PROD
entertainment	I-PROD
system	I-PROD
in	O
1990	O
,	O
the	O
series	O
currently	O
consists	O
of	O
sixteen	O
core	O
entries	O
and	O
four	O
spinoffs	O
.	O

#	id	227
five	O
players	O
participated	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
won	O
by	O
stephen	B-PER
hendry	I-PER
.	O

#	id	228
she	O
also	O
appeared	O
in	O
episodes	O
of	O
z-cars	B-CW
,	O
the	B-CW
bill	I-CW
and	O
kessler	B-CW
.	O

#	id	229
the	B-GRP
wichita	I-GRP
eagle	I-GRP
,	O
major	O
regional	O
newspaper	O
from	O
wichita	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	230
censuses	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
bible	B-CW
.	O

#	id	231
it	O
is	O
situated	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
bank	O
of	O
the	O
rhine	B-LOC
,	O
approx	O
.	O
7	O
km	O
southeast	O
of	O
ludwigshafen	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	232
the	O
album	O
was	O
released	O
in	O
1990	O
by	O
sparrow	B-CORP
records	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	233
this	O
is	O
a	O
list	O
of	O
castles	O
in	O
east	B-LOC
dunbartonshire	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	234
he	O
was	O
also	O
strongly	O
influenced	O
by	O
the	O
genius	O
of	O
antonio	B-PER
da	I-PER
correggio	I-PER
and	O
by	O
the	O
masterworks	O
by	O
melozzo	B-PER
da	I-PER
forlì	I-PER
.	O

#	id	236
harvey	O
began	O
providing	O
video	O
commentary	O
for	O
the	O
website	O
of	O
the	B-CORP
washington	I-CORP
post	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	237
bryan	B-PER
sutton	I-PER
banjo	O
,	O
acoustic	O
guitar	O
,	O
mandolin	O

#	id	238
boeing	O
737	O
800	O
of	O
skymark	B-CORP
airlines	I-CORP
at	O
the	O
airport	O
]	O
]	O

#	id	239
for	O
a	O
while	O
he	O
runs	O
a	O
pirate	B-CORP
radio	I-CORP
station	O
(	O
troy	O
fm	O
)	O
from	O
the	O
airing	O
cupboard	O
but	O
the	O
bad	O
wiring	O
causes	O
him	O
continual	O
problems	O
,	O
finally	O
culminating	O
in	O
an	O
explosion	O
.	O

#	id	240
will	O
be	O
replaced	O
by	O
land	B-PROD
rover	I-PROD
defender	I-PROD
(l316)	I-PROD
.	O

#	id	241
they	O
have	O
teamed	O
up	O
with	O
oddworld	B-CORP
inhabitants	I-CORP
,	O
to	O
recreate	O
the	O
series	O
in	O
high	O
definition	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
working	O
on	O
new	O
installments	O
in	O
the	O
series	O
.	O

#	id	242
voima	O
was	O
built	O
to	O
the	O
highest	O
ice	O
class	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
lloyd's	B-CORP
register	I-CORP
1a	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
fully	O
welded	O
hull	O
and	O
shell	O
plating	O
measuring	O
in	O
thickness	O
in	O
the	O
ice	O
belt	O
.	O

#	id	243
they	O
received	O
a	O
favorable	O
review	O
in	O
the	B-CORP
washington	I-CORP
post	I-CORP
,	O
and	O
their	O
performances	O
were	O
successful	O
.	O

#	id	244
he	O
lost	O
his	O
job	O
the	O
following	O
year	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
an	O
assault	O
outside	O
a	O
bar	O
in	O
dundee	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	245
grovesite	O
signed	O
its	O
first	O
two	O
large	O
customers	O
,	O
bearingpoint	B-CORP
and	O
target	B-CORP
,	O
within	O
a	O
year	O
of	O
its	O
2003	O
launch	O
.	O

#	id	246
the	O
hebrew	B-GRP
university	I-GRP
of	I-GRP
jerusalem	I-GRP
was	O
involved	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
research	O
seasons	O
.	O

#	id	247
the	O
barcelona	B-LOC
pavilion	I-LOC
,	O
designed	O
by	O
ludwig	B-PER
mies	I-PER
van	I-PER
der	I-PER
rohe	I-PER
.	O

#	id	248
the	O
showing	O
of	O
the	O
film	O
was	O
preceded	O
by	O
live	O
music	O
,	O
a	O
dance	O
contest	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parade	O
of	O
chevrolet	B-PROD
corvette	I-PROD
carrying	O
residents	O
who	O
had	O
worked	O
on	O
the	O
film	O
.	O

#	id	249
it	O
includes	O
six	O
recorded	O
songs	O
and	O
two	O
live	O
songs	O
,	O
recorded	O
at	O
eddie's	B-CORP
attic	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	250
forbidden	B-CW
lover	I-CW
,	O
a	O
1998	O
single	O
by	O
l	O
arc	O
en	O
ciel	O

#	id	251
slovenia	O
has	O
an	O
honorary	O
consulate	O
in	O
haifa	B-LOC
and	O
in	O
tel	B-LOC
aviv	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	252
mount	B-PER
sims	I-PER
–	O
engineering	O
,	O
live	O
percussion	O
re	O
editing	O
,	O
mixing	O
,	O
production	O
;	O
halldorophone	O
re	O
editing	O
;	O
vocals	O

#	id	254
established	O
in	O
1972	O
,	O
the	O
pakistan	B-GRP
naval	I-GRP
air	I-GRP
arm	I-GRP
provides	O
fleet	O
air	O
defence	O
,	O
maritime	O
reconnaissance	O
,	O
and	O
anti	O
submarine	O
warfare	O
capability	O
.	O

#	id	256
the	O
edifice	O
stores	O
artefacts	O
of	O
the	O
colonial	O
era	O
such	O
as	O
ceramic	B-PROD
bathtubs	O
,	O
etc	O
.	O

#	id	257
barton	B-LOC
,	O
a	O
village	O
and	O
civil	O
parish	O

#	id	258
it	O
stars	O
shaina	B-PER
magdayao	I-PER
in	O
the	O
title	O
role	O
.	O

#	id	260
the	O
horror	O
in	O
the	O
white	O
chamber	O
is	O
heavily	O
influenced	O
by	O
the	O
game	O
series	O
,	O
silent	B-CW
hill	I-CW
by	O
konami	B-CORP
and	O
the	O
movie	O
event	B-CW
horizon	I-CW
.	O

#	id	261
it	O
has	O
not	O
the	O
epistula	B-CW
ad	I-CW
carpianum	I-CW
.	O

#	id	263
ace	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
base	I-GRP
,	O
céline	B-PER
dion	I-PER
,	O
haddaway	B-PER
,	O
meat	B-PER
loaf	I-PER
and	O
tori	B-PER
amos	I-PER
were	O
among	O
the	O
other	O
artists	O
who	O
had	O
multiple	O
top	O
10	O
entries	O
in	O
1994	O
.	O

#	id	264
yeah	B-GRP
yeah	I-GRP
yeahs	I-GRP
–	O
sacrilege	B-CW
(	O
director	O
of	O
photography	O
:	O
alexis	B-PER
zabe	I-PER
)	O

#	id	265
1999	O
–	O
harry	B-CW
potter	I-CW
and	I-CW
the	I-CW
chamber	I-CW
of	I-CW
secrets	I-CW
–	O
j.	B-PER
k.	I-PER
rowling	I-PER
(	O
bloomsbury	O
)	O

#	id	266
now	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
playing	O
for	O
hc	B-GRP
kometa	I-GRP
brno	I-GRP
(	O
czech	O
republic	O
)	O

#	id	267
he	O
began	O
his	O
career	O
in	O
2009	O
at	O
fc	B-GRP
dacia	I-GRP
chișinău	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	268
the	O
aujon	B-LOC
flows	O
northwestward	O
through	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
commune	O
;	O
the	O
village	O
lies	O
on	O
its	O
left	O
bank	O
.	O

#	id	269
he	O
joined	O
the	O
faculty	O
of	O
franklin	B-GRP
&	I-GRP
marshall	I-GRP
college	I-GRP
as	O
a	O
professor	O
of	O
social	O
science	O
in	O
1892	O
.	O

#	id	270
he	O
is	O
also	O
chairman	O
of	O
the	O
trustees	O
of	O
the	O
think	B-GRP
tank	I-GRP
respublica	B-CORP
.	O

#	id	271
it	O
occurs	O
in	O
bolivia	B-LOC
,	O
brazil	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
suriname	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	272
soft	O
sighing	O
motif	B-CW
of	O
the	O
violins	O
,	O
an	O
echo	O
of	O
the	O
singing	O
,	O
drop	O
into	O
these	O
rests	O
.	O

#	id	275
wrexham	O
manager	O
brian	B-PER
carey	I-PER
said	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
well	O
covered	O
in	O
terms	O
of	O
strikers	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
some	O
way	O
down	O
the	O
pecking	O
order	O
.	O

#	id	276
he	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
storyboard	O
artist	O
for	O
the	O
animated	O
series	O
kim	B-CW
possible	I-CW
and	O
worked	O
on	O
the	O
character	O
layout	O
for	O
king	B-CW
of	I-CW
the	I-CW
hill	I-CW
.	O

#	id	277
a	O
year	O
later	O
,	O
the	O
unions	O
merged	O
their	O
locals	O
in	O
missoula	B-LOC
as	O
an	O
experiment	O
and	O
trial	O
run	O
for	O
a	O
possible	O
statewide	O
merger	O
.	O

#	id	278
it	O
supports	O
european	B-GRP
union	I-GRP
and	O
a	O
strong	O
partnership	O
with	O
the	O
united	B-LOC
states	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
america	I-LOC
within	O
the	O
framework	O
of	O
nato	B-GRP
.	O

#	id	279
you're	B-CW
next	I-CW
centers	O
on	O
a	O
family	O
reunion	O
,	O
that	O
goes	O
terribly	O
wrong	O
once	O
a	O
group	O
of	O
mysterious	O
masked	O
killers	O
start	O
killing	O
off	O
each	O
person	O
one	O
by	O
one	O
.	O

#	id	280
exiled	O
to	O
the	O
minors	O
,	O
he	O
spent	O
the	O
next	O
two	O
seasons	O
in	O
the	O
international	B-GRP
hockey	I-GRP
league	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	282
for	O
air	B-PROD
conditioning	I-PROD
and	O
other	O
electrical	O
needs	O
,	O
it	O
chose	O
to	O
employ	O
independent	O
diesel	O
generators	O
in	O
each	O
car	O
.	O

#	id	283
the	O
fire	O
also	O
affected	O
the	O
areas	O
of	O
saltmarket	B-LOC
and	O
gallowgate	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	284
he	O
has	O
previously	O
represented	O
the	O
afghanistan	B-GRP
national	I-GRP
cricket	I-GRP
team	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	285
just	O
before	O
7	O
:	O
00am	O
,	O
in	O
sonning	B-LOC
cutting	O
,	O
the	O
train	O
ran	O
into	O
soil	O
that	O
had	O
slipped	O
from	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
cutting	O
onto	O
the	O
track	O
,	O
covering	O
it	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
feet	O
deep	O
.	O

#	id	286
reyes	O
received	O
her	O
m.f.a.	O
at	O
san	B-GRP
francisco	I-GRP
state	I-GRP
university	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	290
ellen	O
's	O
great	O
grandson	O
,	O
tim	B-PER
henman	I-PER
is	O
a	O
popular	O
retired	O
tennis	O
player	O
.	O

#	id	291
live	O
!	O
in	O
new	B-LOC
orleans	I-LOC
,	O
emeril	B-PER
lagasse	I-PER
,	O
pete	B-PER
fountain	I-PER
,	O
kyle	B-PER
busch	I-PER

#	id	292
metropolitan	B-GRP
state	I-GRP
university	I-GRP
of	I-GRP
denver	I-GRP
,	O
university	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
colorado	I-GRP
denver	I-GRP
,	O
university	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
colorado,	I-GRP
colorado	I-GRP
springs	I-GRP
,	O
university	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
denver	I-GRP
†	O

#	id	295
in	O
1961	O
,	O
jane	B-PER
jacobs	I-PER
published	O
the	B-CW
death	I-CW
and	I-CW
life	I-CW
of	I-CW
great	I-CW
american	I-CW
cities	I-CW
.	O

#	id	296
it	O
quickly	O
became	O
a	O
chart	O
topper	O
on	O
billboard	B-CW
s	O
hot	O
dance	O
/	O
disco	O
chart	O
.	O

#	id	297
sonetts	O
shared	O
engines	O
and	O
other	O
components	O
with	O
saab	B-PROD
93	I-PROD
,	O
saab	B-PROD
95	I-PROD
and	O
saab	B-PROD
96	I-PROD
of	O
the	O
same	O
era	O
.	O

#	id	299
the	B-GRP
honolulu	I-GRP
advertiser	I-GRP
wrote	O
that	O
those	O
who	O
saw	O
her	O
perform	O
typically	O
speak	O
about	O
the	O
almost	O
mystical	O
experience	O
she	O
seemed	O
to	O
channel	O
.	O

#	id	300
astrazeneca	B-CORP
pharmaceuticals	O
(	O
3.9	O
%	O
stake	O
,	O
3.9	O
%	O
voting	O
rights	O
)	O

#	id	301
this	O
aircraft	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
1963	O
for	O
the	O
film	O
those	B-CW
magnificent	I-CW
men	I-CW
in	I-CW
their	I-CW
flying	I-CW
machines	I-CW
.	O
]	O
]	O

#	id	302
however	O
,	O
they	O
lost	O
to	O
esteghlal	B-GRP
khuzestan	I-GRP
f.c.	I-GRP
to	O
miss	O
the	O
qualification	O
.	O

#	id	304
by	O
1900	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
worked	O
as	O
a	O
clerk	O
for	O
the	O
central	B-CORP
railroad	I-CORP
of	I-CORP
new	I-CORP
jersey	I-CORP
,	O
had	O
moved	O
the	O
family	O
to	O
the	O
township	O
of	O
linden	B-LOC
in	O
that	O
state	O
.	O

#	id	306
common	O
root	O
rot	O
is	O
a	O
disease	O
of	O
wheat	B-PROD
caused	O
by	O
one	O
or	O
more	O
fungi	O
.	O

#	id	307
i	B-CW
should	I-CW
care	I-CW
(	O
sammy	B-PER
cahn	I-PER
,	O
axel	B-PER
stordahl	I-PER
,	O
paul	B-PER
weston	I-PER
)	O
9	O
:	O
00	O

#	id	308
other	O
artists	O
that	O
he	O
produced	O
include	O
justin	B-PER
hinds	I-PER
(	O
just	O
in	O
time	O
/	O
jezebel	O
)	O
,	O
the	B-GRP
gaylads	I-GRP
,	O
the	B-GRP
heptones	I-GRP
,	O
and	O
big	B-PER
youth	I-PER
.	O

#	id	310
the	O
film	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
box	B-CW
office	I-CW
bomb	I-CW
,	O
grossing	O
$	O
119	O
million	O
against	O
a	O
budget	O
of	O
$	O
80	O
100	O
million	O
.	O

#	id	311
in	O
2001	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
independent	O
film	O
titled	O
songcatcher	B-CW
,	O
with	O
janet	B-PER
mcteer	I-PER
.	O

#	id	312
the	O
town	O
was	O
a	O
halting	O
place	O
on	O
the	O
pilgrimage	O
to	O
santiago	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
compostela	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	314
bastien	O
lepage	O
painted	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
native	O
village	O
of	O
damvillers	B-LOC
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
written	O
in	O
the	O
work	O
's	O
lower	O
left	O
corner	O
just	O
above	O
the	O
artist	O
's	O
signature	O
.	O

#	id	316
in	O
1993	O
aschehoug	B-CORP
chief	O
william	B-PER
nygaard	I-PER
was	O
shot	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
but	O
survived	O
.	O

#	id	317
the	O
final	O
rankings	O
for	O
entries	O
placing	O
between	O
10th	O
position	O
and	O
4th	O
position	O
were	O
never	O
revealed	O
,	O
although	O
avvenire	B-GRP
later	O
published	O
an	O
article	O
listing	O
televote	O
results	O
.	O

#	id	319
defrancesco	O
was	O
16	O
years	O
old	O
when	O
he	O
signed	O
an	O
exclusive	O
recording	O
contract	O
with	O
columbia	B-CORP
records	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	320
the	O
purse	O
for	O
the	O
tournament	O
was	O
us	O
$	O
150,000	O
,	O
with	O
$	O
25,000	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
winner	O
,	O
don	B-PER
january	I-PER
.	O

#	id	321
1974	O
:	O
columbo,	B-CW
season	I-CW
3	I-CW
(	O
tv	O
movie	O
)	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
.	O

#	id	322
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
five	O
founders	O
of	O
vmware	B-CORP
inc.	I-CORP
in	O
1998	O
(	O
with	O
his	O
advisor	O
mendel	B-PER
rosenblum	I-PER
)	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
chief	O
architect	O
until	O
2004	O
.	O

#	id	323
all	O
vocals	O
,	O
keyboards	O
and	O
synthesizers	O
by	O
marvin	B-PER
gaye	I-PER

#	id	324
there	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
control	O
rope	B-PROD
of	O
whichever	O
sail	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
with	O
is	O
run	O
through	O
a	O
fitting	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
spinnaker	O
pole	O
.	O

#	id	325
most	O
of	O
the	O
music	O
was	O
recorded	O
into	O
a	O
apple	B-PROD
macintosh	I-PROD
computer	O
using	O
a	O
board	O
and	O
manipulated	O
with	O
music	O
editor	O
programs	O
on	O
the	O
computer	O
.	O

#	id	326
lumber	B-PROD
was	O
the	O
principal	O
industry	O
with	O
at	O
least	O
17	O
sawmill	B-CORP
in	O
the	O
area	O
.	O

#	id	329
he	O
currently	O
plays	O
for	O
lowestoft	B-GRP
town	I-GRP
f.c.	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	330
he	O
was	O
awarded	O
the	O
order	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
the	I-GRP
badge	I-GRP
of	I-GRP
honour	I-GRP
and	O
the	O
order	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
the	I-GRP
red	I-GRP
banner	I-GRP
of	I-GRP
labour	I-GRP
by	O
the	O
soviet	B-LOC
union	I-LOC
government	O
.	O

#	id	331
the	O
yield	O
of	O
this	O
reaction	O
can	O
be	O
improved	O
by	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
zinc	B-PROD
as	O
the	O
dehalogenating	O
agent	O
and	O
sodium	O
iodide	O
as	O
a	O
catalyst	O
.	O

#	id	332
belgrade	B-LOC
,	O
then	O
in	O
socialist	B-LOC
federal	I-LOC
republic	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
yugoslavia	I-LOC
,	O
now	O
in	O
serbia	B-LOC

#	id	333
he	O
appeared	O
on	O
an	O
nhk	B-CORP
drama	O
series	O
in	O
2000	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
starred	O
in	O
several	O
movies	O
since	O
then	O
.	O

#	id	334
until	O
2009	O
,	O
the	O
team	O
used	O
cervélo	B-CORP
bikes	O
and	O
shimano	B-CORP
components	O
.	O

#	id	335
file	O
:	O
couscoussier	O
.	O
jpg	O
|	O
a	O
couscoussier	B-PROD
,	O
a	O
type	O
of	O
steamer	O
used	O
to	O
cook	O
couscous	B-PROD

#	id	337
taito	B-CORP
corporation	I-CORP
contributed	O
well	O
received	O
ports	O
such	O
as	O
space	B-CW
invaders	I-CW
and	O
densha	B-CW
de	I-CW
go!	I-CW
.	O

#	id	339
a	O
force	O
play	O
provided	O
the	O
second	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
inning	O
but	O
boog	B-PER
powell	I-PER
single	O
drove	O
in	O
one	O
run	O
.	O

#	id	340
fry	O
–	O
this	O
setting	O
can	O
be	O
used	O
to	O
fry	O
meat	O
,	O
poultry	B-PROD
,	O
fish	O
,	O
vegetables	O
,	O
and	O
seafood	O
.	O

#	id	341
zsc	B-GRP
lions	I-GRP
qualified	O
for	O
the	O
final	O
round	O
.	O

#	id	342
new	O
york	O
:	O
st.	B-CORP
martin's	I-CORP
press	I-CORP
,	O
1993	O
.	O
.	O

#	id	343
out	B-CW
of	I-CW
nowhere	I-CW
(	O
johnny	B-PER
green	I-PER
,	O
edward	B-PER
heyman	I-PER
)	O
6	O
:	O
41	O

#	id	345
gerry	B-PER
taggart	I-PER
,	O
brian	B-PER
deane	I-PER
;	O
(	O
nicky	B-PER
summerbee	I-PER
sent	O
off	O
)	O

#	id	347
this	O
locomotive	O
and	O
others	O
built	O
by	O
the	O
firm	O
were	O
initially	O
copies	O
of	O
2-2-0	B-PROD
types	O
(	O
2	O
2	O
0s	O
)	O
.	O

#	id	348
she	O
dies	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
her	O
son	O
is	O
shot	O
in	O
morbihan	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	349
events	O
from	O
the	O
year	O
1835	O
in	O
denmark	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	350
the	O
riding	O
consists	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
parksville	B-LOC
,	O
the	O
town	O
of	O
qualicum	B-LOC
beach	I-LOC
and	O
the	O
communities	O
of	O
lantzville,	B-LOC
british	I-LOC
columbia	I-LOC
and	O
nanoose	B-LOC
bay,	I-LOC
british	I-LOC
columbia	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	351
draw	O
in	O
the	O
headquarters	O
of	O
the	O
brazilian	B-GRP
football	I-GRP
confederation	I-GRP
(	O
regulations	O
article	O
17	O
)	O
.	O

#	id	352
beenox	B-CORP
confirmed	O
that	O
the	O
character	O
was	O
excluded	O
from	O
the	O
plot	O
so	O
the	O
game	O
does	O
nt	O
generate	O
spoilers	O
for	O
the	O
then	O
upcoming	O
film	O
.	O

#	id	353
dust	B-CW
in	I-CW
the	I-CW
wind	I-CW
(	O
livgren	O
)	O
–	O
3	O
:	O
27	O

#	id	355
he	O
was	O
buried	O
in	O
lake	B-LOC
charles	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	356
it	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
world	B-CW
health	I-CW
organization	I-CW
model	I-CW
list	I-CW
of	I-CW
essential	I-CW
medicines	I-CW
.	O

#	id	357
fifteen	O
years	O
later	O
,	O
zoltán	B-PER
tibor	I-PER
balogh	I-PER
succeeded	O
in	O
showing	O
that	O
conjectures	O
and	O
are	O
true	O
.	O

#	id	358
this	O
eventually	O
led	O
to	O
his	O
signing	O
to	O
interscope	B-CORP
records	I-CORP
in	O
2012	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
named	O
an	O
xxl	B-CW
later	O
that	O
year	O
.	O

#	id	359
the	O
company	O
started	O
work	O
on	O
a	O
second	O
game	O
,	O
p.i.d.	O
(	O
short	O
for	O
private	O
investigator	O
dollarally	O
)	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
published	O
by	O
renegade	B-CORP
software	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	360
it	O
was	O
examined	O
and	O
described	O
by	O
bernard	B-PER
de	I-PER
montfaucon	I-PER
,	O
johann	B-PER
jakob	I-PER
wettstein	I-PER
,	O
johann	B-PER
martin	I-PER
augustin	I-PER
scholz	I-PER
,	O
paulin	B-PER
martin	I-PER
,	O
and	O
henri	B-PER
omont	I-PER
.	O

#	id	361
ralt	B-GRP
dominated	O
almost	O
every	O
season	O
fielding	O
the	O
most	O
cars	O
out	O
of	O
any	O
constructor	O
.	O

#	id	362
in	O
2012	O
,	O
the	O
chevrolet	B-PROD
cobalt	I-PROD
was	O
added	O
to	O
the	O
production	O
line	O
.	O

#	id	363
while	O
running	O
a	O
plantation	O
,	O
he	O
engaged	O
in	O
mercantile	O
pursuits	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
operation	O
of	O
sawmill	B-CORP
and	O
steamboat	B-PROD
.	O

#	id	364
small	O
town	O
talk	O
by	O
shannon	B-PER
mcnally	I-PER
and	O
dr.	B-PER
john	I-PER
.	O

#	id	365
he	O
began	O
his	O
professional	O
career	O
in	O
2004	O
with	O
lokomotiv	B-GRP
yaroslavl	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	366
she	O
also	O
known	O
as	O
host	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
segments	O
in	O
star	B-CW
golden	I-CW
bell	I-CW
.	O

#	id	367
professionally	O
built	O
wood-fired	B-PROD
oven	I-PROD
with	O
sawdust	O
hoppers	O
were	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
early	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
20th	O
century	O
.	O

#	id	369
he	O
also	O
had	O
supporting	O
roles	O
in	O
films	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
good	B-CW
night,	I-CW
and	I-CW
good	I-CW
luck.	I-CW
and	O
argo	B-CW
.	O

#	id	370
the	O
crew	O
intended	O
the	O
movie	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
continuation	O
of	O
the	O
season	O
five	O
finale	O
the	B-CW
end	I-CW
,	O
but	O
was	O
also	O
meant	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
its	O
own	O
.	O

#	id	372
he	O
quickly	O
moved	O
up	O
the	O
ranks	O
and	O
worked	O
as	O
an	O
executive	O
producer	O
at	O
american	B-CORP
broadcasting	I-CORP
company	I-CORP
and	O
at	O
screen	B-GRP
gems	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	373
in	O
2001	O
,	O
16	O
year	O
old	O
kyle	B-PER
busch	I-PER
dominated	O
the	O
race	O
but	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
fuel	O
with	O
20	O
laps	O
to	O
go	O
.	O

#	id	374
the	O
floods	O
affected	O
seven	O
regions	O
of	O
namibia	B-LOC
,	O
three	O
provinces	O
of	O
zambia	B-LOC
,	O
two	O
regions	O
of	O
angola	B-LOC
and	O
part	O
of	O
botswana	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	375
boots	O
was	O
the	O
biggest	O
chemist	O
chain	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
now	O
a.s.	B-CORP
watson	I-CORP
group	I-CORP
is	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
biggest	O
health	O
retail	O
company	O
.	O

#	id	376
arches	O
with	O
beautiful	O
moulding	O
were	O
hidden	O
by	O
walls	O
,	O
sedilia	B-PROD
were	O
removed	O
from	O
their	O
original	O
positions	O
and	O
reredos	O
had	O
been	O
covered	O
with	O
plaster	O
or	O
hidden	O
with	O
walls	O
.	O

#	id	377
he	O
subsequently	O
played	O
for	O
chelmsford	B-GRP
city	I-GRP
f.c.	I-GRP
from	O
1986	O
to	O
1988	O
.	O

#	id	379
the	O
bbc	B-CORP
also	O
filmed	O
her	O
in	O
costume	O
singing	O
arias	O
from	O
the	O
opera	O
for	O
a	O
1951	O
episode	O
of	O
picture	B-CW
page	I-CW
.	O

#	id	380
hornet	O
appears	O
as	O
an	O
additional	O
costume	O
in	O
the	B-CW
amazing	I-CW
spider-man	I-CW
2	I-CW
video	O
game	O
.	O

#	id	382
his	O
compositional	O
output	O
includes	O
several	O
orchestra	B-GRP
,	O
chamber	B-CW
music	I-CW
,	O
and	O
works	O
for	O
solo	O
piano	O
.	O

#	id	383
by	O
1971	O
,	O
he	O
relocated	O
to	O
australia	B-LOC
continuing	O
to	O
perform	O
at	O
festivals	O
.	O

#	id	384
this	O
is	O
an	O
index	O
of	O
dos	B-CW
games	O
.	O

#	id	385
the	O
top	O
10	O
national	B-GRP
paralympic	I-GRP
committee	I-GRP
by	O
number	O
of	O
gold	O
medals	O
are	O
listed	O
below	O
.	O

#	id	386
her	O
film	O
career	O
includes	O
roles	O
in	O
the	B-CW
greek	I-CW
tycoon	I-CW
and	O
cliff	B-PER
twemlow	I-PER
.	O

#	id	387
windows	B-CW
2000	I-CW
appears	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
working	O
driver	O
.	O

#	id	388
except	O
track	O
7	O
performed	O
by	O
the	O
the	B-GRP
yardbirds	I-GRP

#	id	389
the	O
game	O
uses	O
a	O
battery	O
packed	O
random-access	B-PROD
memory	I-PROD
in	O
order	O
to	O
save	O
progress	O
.	O

#	id	390
:	O
crusoe	B-CW
–	O
sound	O
engineering	O
.	O

#	id	391
parry	O
thomas	O
became	O
chief	O
engineer	O
at	O
leyland	B-CORP
motors	I-CORP
,	O
a	O
company	O
whose	O
main	O
products	O
were	O
commercial	O
vehicles	O
.	O

#	id	392
the	O
fight	O
was	O
the	O
main	O
event	O
on	O
a	O
card	O
televised	O
on	O
sky	B-CORP
sports	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	393
running	O
a	O
distant	O
second	O
are	O
adaptations	O
of	O
the	O
1872	O
novel	O
carmilla	B-CW
by	O
sheridan	B-PER
le	I-PER
fanu	I-PER
.	O

#	id	394
a	O
live	O
version	O
by	O
etta	B-PER
james	I-PER
is	O
included	O
on	O
her	O
1963	O
album	O
etta	B-CW
james	I-CW
rocks	I-CW
the	I-CW
house	I-CW
.	O

#	id	395
then	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
songwriter	O
and	O
arranger	O
shows	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
song	O
,	O
non,	B-CW
je	I-CW
ne	I-CW
regrette	I-CW
rien	I-CW
,	O
and	O
édith	O
exclaims	O
:	O
youre	O
marvelous	O
!	O

#	id	396
its	O
seat	O
is	O
the	O
town	O
of	O
krzywiń	B-LOC
,	O
which	O
lies	O
approximately	O
south	O
east	O
of	O
kościan	B-LOC
and	O
south	O
of	O
the	O
regional	O
capital	O
poznań	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	397
mutsu	B-PROD
(	O
indo	O
apple	O
×	O
golden	O
delicious	O
)	O

#	id	398
eventually	O
the	O
part	O
went	O
to	O
angie	B-PER
dickinson	I-PER
,	O
who	O
had	O
just	O
impressed	O
in	O
rio	B-CW
bravo	I-CW
.	O

#	id	399
wallace	O
's	O
1869	O
the	B-CW
malay	I-CW
archipelago	I-CW
by	O
john	B-PER
gerrard	I-PER
keulemans	I-PER
]	O
]	O

#	id	400
jane	B-PER
fonda	I-PER
–	O
julia	B-CW
as	O
lillian	B-PER
hellman	I-PER

#	id	401
pinnacle	B-CORP
sports	I-CORP
,	O
an	O
online	O
gaming	O
website	O

#	id	402
he	O
became	O
a	O
co	O
executive	O
producer	O
for	O
the	O
drama	O
series	O
miami	B-CW
medical	I-CW
which	O
aired	O
as	O
a	O
mid	O
season	O
replacement	O
in	O
2010	O
.	O

#	id	404
”	O
murder	B-CW
most	I-CW
foul	I-CW
”	O
,	O
written	O
by	O
bob	B-PER
dylan	I-PER
,	O
alludes	O
to	O
the	O
events	O
around	O
kennedy	O
’s	O
assassination	O
throughout	O
the	O
song	O

#	id	405
it	O
is	O
4	O
km	O
southwest	O
of	O
nea	B-LOC
kios	I-LOC
,	O
9	O
km	O
south	O
of	O
argos	B-LOC
and	O
8	O
km	O
west	O
of	O
nauplion	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	407
her	O
last	O
major	O
role	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
guest	O
appearance	O
on	O
the	O
television	O
series	O
jack	B-CW
of	I-CW
all	I-CW
trades	I-CW
in	O
2000	O
.	O

#	id	408
it	O
is	O
published	O
by	O
world	B-GRP
scientific	I-GRP
and	O
covers	O
information	O
processing	O
in	O
natural	O
and	O
artificial	O
neural	O
systems	O
.	O

#	id	409
before	O
it	O
was	O
published	O
,	O
steven	B-PER
spielberg	I-PER
(	O
dreamworks	B-GRP
)	O
acquired	O
film	O
rights	O
to	O
the	O
novel	O
.	O

#	id	411
her	O
records	O
from	O
the	O
1980s	O
have	O
been	O
described	O
as	O
being	O
influenced	O
by	O
prince	B-PER
,	O
as	O
her	O
producers	O
are	O
ex	O
members	O
of	O
the	B-GRP
time	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	413
the	O
draw	O
was	O
split	O
up	O
into	O
four	O
sections	O
:	O
teams	O
from	O
the	O
north	O
,	O
the	O
center	O
,	O
the	O
south	O
and	O
the	O
azores	B-LOC
region	O
.	O

#	id	414
the	O
place	O
was	O
then	O
became	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
bruneian	B-LOC
empire	I-LOC
in	O
the	O
13th	O
century	O
.	O

#	id	415
team	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
:	O
pfc	B-GRP
cska	I-GRP
moscow	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	417
before	O
joining	O
academia	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
12	O
years	O
in	O
sales	O
and	O
marketing	O
management	O
positions	O
with	O
ibm	B-CORP
,	O
groupe	B-CORP
bull	I-CORP
and	O
hitachi	B-CORP
.	O

#	id	418
a	O
four	O
track	O
extended	B-CW
play	I-CW
was	O
released	O
digitally	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O

#	id	419
whores	O
taken	O
from	O
jane's	B-CW
addiction	I-CW
,	O
1987	O

#	id	420
it	O
was	O
directed	O
by	O
paul	B-PER
wendkos	I-PER
.	O

#	id	421
it	O
is	O
considered	O
a	O
lost	B-CW
film	I-CW
.	O

#	id	422
the	O
ten	O
episode	O
series	O
was	O
produced	O
for	O
the	O
discovery	B-CORP
channel	I-CORP
,	O
and	O
first	O
broadcast	O
in	O
2004	O
.	O

#	id	423
his	O
final	O
reelection	O
campaign	O
,	O
against	O
then	O
councilman	O
cory	B-PER
booker	I-PER
in	O
2002	O
,	O
was	O
documented	O
in	O
the	O
2005	O
feature	O
film	O
street	B-CW
fight	I-CW
.	O

#	id	425
since	O
1993	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
representative	O
office	O
in	O
moscow	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	426
he	O
previously	O
played	O
for	O
the	O
canberra	B-GRP
raiders	I-GRP
,	O
penrith	B-GRP
panthers	I-GRP
,	O
bradford	B-GRP
bulls	I-GRP
and	O
the	O
london	B-GRP
broncos	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	427
andrew	O
also	O
appeared	O
as	O
the	O
soccer	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
previous	O
co	O
star	O
from	O
the	B-CW
trigger	I-CW
effect	I-CW
dermot	B-PER
mulroney	I-PER
played	O
the	O
father	O
of	O
the	O
main	O
character	O
.	O

#	id	428
markle	O
married	O
actress	O
melinda	B-PER
culea	I-PER
in	O
1996	O
.	O

#	id	429
dino	O
was	O
invited	O
to	O
opet	O
the	O
new	O
arena	O
in	O
zenica	B-LOC
with	O
a	O
concert	O
.	O

#	id	430
the	O
country	O
's	O
patron	O
saint	O
is	O
fyodor	B-PER
karamazov	I-PER
.	O

#	id	431
some	O
varieties	O
of	O
johnnycake	B-PROD
resemble	O
doughnuts	O
.	O

#	id	432
hizan	O
(	O
)	O
is	O
a	O
town	O
and	O
a	O
district	O
of	O
bitlis	B-LOC
province	I-LOC
,	O
turkey	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	434
sweet	B-CW
home	I-CW
alabama	I-CW
performed	O
by	O
lynyrd	B-GRP
skynyrd	I-GRP
–	O
4	O
:	O
43	O

#	id	435
windows	B-CW
7	I-CW
and	O
later	O
(	O
ia	O
32	O
,	O
x64	O
)	O
,	O
windows	B-CW
server	I-CW
2008	I-CW
r2	I-CW
and	O
later	O
(	O
x64	O
)	O

#	id	436
most	O
of	O
the	O
manuscript	O
was	O
not	O
original	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
compendium	B-CW
of	O
12th	O
century	O
knowledge	O
.	O

#	id	437
it	O
is	O
68	O
km	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
nearest	O
major	O
population	O
center	O
,	O
pirapora	B-LOC
at	O
an	O
elevation	O
of	O
690	O
meters	O
.	O

#	id	438
this	O
is	O
a	O
list	O
of	O
characters	O
in	O
leo	B-PER
tolstoy	I-PER
1869	O
novel	O
war	B-CW
and	I-CW
peace	I-CW
.	O

#	id	439
shortly	O
afterwards	O
,	O
fannie	B-CORP
mae	I-CORP
and	O
freddie	B-CORP
mac	I-CORP
barred	O
lenders	O
and	O
servicers	O
from	O
using	O
the	O
firm	O
for	O
foreclosures	O
.	O

#	id	440
germany	O
became	O
a	O
great	B-GRP
power	I-GRP
,	O
boasting	O
a	O
rapidly	O
developing	O
rail	O
network	O
,	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
strongest	O
army	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
fast	O
growing	O
industrial	O
base	O
.	O

#	id	441
train	O
services	O
are	O
operated	O
by	O
trenitalia	B-GRP
.	O

#	id	442
las	B-CW
juanas	I-CW
(	O
august	O
20	O
,	O
2018	O
–	O
present	O
)	O

#	id	443
the	O
film	O
stars	O
rose	B-PER
mcgowan	I-PER
,	O
michael	B-PER
eklund	I-PER
,	O
christopher	B-PER
lloyd	I-PER
,	O
and	O
richard	B-PER
gunn	I-PER
.	O

#	id	444
kial	O
spent	O
the	O
first	O
17	O
seasons	O
of	O
his	O
professional	O
career	O
with	O
ca	B-GRP
bordj	I-GRP
bou	I-GRP
arréridj	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	445
2tph	O
to	O
,	O
all	O
stations	O
to	O
hither	B-LOC
green	I-LOC
railway	I-LOC
station	I-LOC
then	O
fast	O
to	O
london	B-LOC
bridge	I-LOC
station	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	446
it	O
closed	O
in	O
1876	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
deeded	O
to	O
willamette	B-GRP
university	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	447
braniff	B-CORP
international	I-CORP
airways	I-CORP
,	O
took	O
this	O
route	O
over	O
in	O
1934	O
.	O

#	id	448
against	O
expectations	O
,	O
farhan	B-PER
akhtar	I-PER
did	O
not	O
lend	O
his	O
voice	O
to	O
the	O
soundtrack	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
in	O
[	O
[	O
rock	O
on	O

#	id	449
he	O
introduced	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
wider	O
public	O
in	O
1961	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
placed	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
citigroup	B-CORP
bank	O
lobbies	O
for	O
six	O
months	O
.	O

#	id	450
in	O
1789	O
,	O
george	B-PER
washington	I-PER
crossed	O
the	O
bridge	O
on	O
his	O
way	O
to	O
his	O
first	O
presidential	O
inauguration	O
in	O
new	B-LOC
york	I-LOC
city	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	452
in	O
1528	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
raised	O
to	O
the	O
rank	O
of	O
a	O
duchy	O
by	O
francis	B-PER
i	I-PER
of	I-PER
france	I-PER
.	O

#	id	453
1	O
–	O
6	O
(	O
writer	O
/	O
artist	O
,	O
2002	O
)	O

#	id	454
an	O
earlier	O
but	O
unrelated	O
star	B-CW
wars:	I-CW
the	I-CW
roleplaying	I-CW
game	I-CW
was	O
published	O
by	O
west	B-CORP
end	I-CORP
games	I-CORP
between	O
1987	O
and	O
1999	O
.	O

#	id	455
in	O
order	O
to	O
meet	O
isambard	B-PER
kingdom	I-PER
brunel	I-PER
strict	O
specifications	O
,	O
an	O
0-4-0	B-PROD
frame	O
carried	O
the	O
engine	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
boiler	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
separate	O
six	O
wheeled	O
frame	O
.	O

#	id	457
mansell	O
was	O
also	O
the	O
catalyst	O
for	O
the	O
breakdown	O
in	O
the	O
relationship	O
between	O
himself	O
and	O
mario	B-PER
andretti	I-PER
.	O

#	id	458
the	O
spicy	O
beef	O
is	O
usually	O
ground	B-PROD
beef	I-PROD
,	O
although	O
a	O
few	O
restaurants	O
and	O
pizzerias	O
tend	O
to	O
use	O
diced	O
beef	O
.	O

#	id	459
kerrang!	B-CW
ranked	O
the	O
album	O
eleventh	O
on	O
their	O
k	O
!	O

#	id	460
it	O
was	O
here	O
that	O
banquets	O
in	O
honour	O
of	O
józef	B-PER
piłsudski	I-PER
,	O
stanisław	B-PER
wojciechowski	I-PER
and	O
józef	B-PER
haller	I-PER
were	O
given	O
.	O

#	id	461
csk	O
then	O
faced	O
the	O
2009	O
champions	O
new	B-GRP
south	I-GRP
wales	I-GRP
cricket	I-GRP
team	I-GRP
in	O
a	O
must	O
win	O
encounter	O
.	O

#	id	463
orsi	B-PER
kocsis	I-PER
(	O
born	O
1984	O
)	O
,	O
fashion	O
,	O
glamour	O
and	O
art	O
nude	O
model	O

#	id	465
:	O
for	O
work	O
after	O
1894	O
,	O
see	O
clinton	B-CORP
and	I-CORP
russell	I-CORP

#	id	466
during	O
the	O
playing	O
beyond	B-CW
sanctorum	I-CW
tour	O
,	O
band	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
few	O
personnel	O
problems	O
.	O

#	id	467
he	O
joined	O
msv	B-GRP
duisburg	I-GRP
for	O
the	O
2014	O
–	O
15	O
season	O
.	O

#	id	468
he	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
kriváň	B-LOC
,	O
detva	B-LOC
district	I-LOC
and	O
died	O
in	O
eger	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	469
the	O
video	O
includes	O
the	O
voice	O
talents	O
of	O
dick	B-PER
clark	I-PER
,	O
robert	B-PER
goulet	I-PER
and	O
james	B-PER
earl	I-PER
jones	I-PER
as	O
well	O
as	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
series	O
regulars	O
.	O

#	id	470
he	O
served	O
as	O
the	O
head	O
football	O
coach	O
at	O
allegheny	B-GRP
college	I-GRP
from	O
2002	O
to	O
2015	O
,	O
compiling	O
a	O
record	O
of	O
62	O
–	O
79	O
.	O

#	id	471
lroc	B-PER
–	O
additional	O
keyboards	O
(	O
track	O
2	O
)	O

#	id	472
a	O
term	O
loan	O
is	O
a	O
monetary	O
loan	B-PROD
that	O
is	O
repaid	O
in	O
regular	O
payments	O
over	O
a	O
set	O
period	O
of	O
time	O
.	O

#	id	473
january	O
5	O
&	O
6	O
,	O
varese	B-LOC
&	O
rome	B-LOC

#	id	475
among	O
his	O
fellow	O
students	O
was	O
maurice	B-PER
ravel	I-PER
,	O
who	O
became	O
his	O
lifelong	O
friend	O
.	O

#	id	476
three	O
volleys	O
from	O
seven	O
rifles	O
were	O
then	O
fired	O
,	O
followed	O
by	O
the	O
playing	O
of	O
taps	B-CW
.	O

#	id	477
colecovision	O
's	O
main	O
competitor	O
was	O
the	O
less	O
commercially	O
successful	O
atari	B-PROD
5200	I-PROD
.	O

#	id	479
sixteen	O
images	O
from	O
the	O
series	O
are	O
included	O
in	O
the	O
science	B-LOC
museum	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
minnesota	I-LOC
exhibition	O
race	O
:	O
are	O
we	O
so	O
different	O
?	O
currently	O
touring	O
nationally	O
.	O

#	id	480
later	O
that	O
month	O
,	O
entertainment	B-CW
weekly	I-CW
released	O
a	O
series	O
of	O
exclusive	O
posters	O
.	O

#	id	481
in	O
mauritania	B-LOC
and	O
yemen	B-LOC
,	O
the	O
track	O
is	O
lower	O
than	O
the	O
typical	O
average	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
any	O
case	O
it	O
gets	O
past	O
the	O
50	O
%	O
state	O
.	O

#	id	482
1991	O
–	O
92	O
micheal	B-PER
ray	I-PER
richardson	I-PER
(	O
kk	O
split	O
)	O
:	O
6.07	O
(	O
in	O
14	O
games	O
)	O

#	id	483
seventeen	O
years	O
later	O
,	O
the	O
old	O
building	O
was	O
dismantled	O
and	O
the	O
present	O
building	O
,	O
designed	O
by	O
fumihiko	B-PER
maki	I-PER
was	O
completed	O
.	O

#	id	484
he	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
brașov	B-LOC
,	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
composer	O
tiberiu	B-PER
brediceanu	I-PER
and	O
grandson	O
of	O
coriolan	B-PER
brediceanu	I-PER
.	O

#	id	485
july	O
6	O
susan	B-PER
ford	I-PER
,	O
daughter	O
of	O
gerald	B-PER
ford	I-PER
,	O
author	O
,	O
photojournalist	O
,	O
and	O
former	O
chair	O
of	O
the	O
board	O
of	O
the	O
betty	B-GRP
ford	I-GRP
center	I-GRP
,	O
in	O
washington,	B-LOC
d.c.	I-LOC

#	id	486
it	O
is	O
the	O
seventh	O
single	O
from	O
his	O
debut	O
studio	O
album	O
lp1	B-CW
.	O

#	id	487
turner	B-CORP
entertainment	I-CORP
supported	O
the	O
show	O
through	O
a	O
massive	O
marketing	O
campaign	O
with	O
thirty	O
three	O
licensees	O
.	O

#	id	488
his	O
wife	O
made	O
the	O
popcorn	B-PROD
.	O

#	id	489
over	O
12	O
seasons	O
,	O
he	O
amassed	O
laliga	B-CORP
totals	O
of	O
244	O
matches	O
and	O
18	O
goals	O
,	O
also	O
representing	O
in	O
the	O
competition	O
real	B-GRP
valladolid	I-GRP
and	O
cádiz	B-GRP
c.f.	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	490
he	O
retired	O
from	O
professional	O
wrestling	O
when	O
the	O
promotion	O
closed	O
in	O
1990	O
and	O
merged	O
with	O
united	B-CORP
states	I-CORP
wrestling	I-CORP
association	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	491
the	O
cincinnati	B-GRP
reds	I-GRP
,	O
whose	O
ballpark	O
was	O
just	O
away	O
across	O
the	O
ohio	B-LOC
river	I-LOC
,	O
blocked	O
the	O
move	O
.	O

#	id	492
this	O
episode	O
was	O
inspired	O
by	O
revelations	O
about	O
cointelpro	B-GRP
and	O
operation	B-GRP
chaos	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	493
gec	O
alsthom	O
subsequently	O
changed	O
its	O
name	O
to	O
alstom	B-CORP
.	O

#	id	495
it	O
was	O
also	O
announced	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
month	O
that	O
angra	B-GRP
guitarist	O
kiko	B-PER
loureiro	I-PER
joined	O
the	O
band	O
.	O

#	id	496
mehdi	B-PER
akhavan-sales	I-PER
,	O
poet	O
(	O
مهدی	O
اخوان	O
ثالث	O
)	O

#	id	497
before	O
1945	O
the	O
area	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
germany	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	499
he	O
later	O
studied	O
law	O
in	O
the	O
university	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
chile	I-GRP
and	O
received	O
his	O
law	O
degree	O
in	O
1959	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
served	O
as	O
a	O
law	O
professor	O
for	O
over	O
30	O
years	O
.	O

#	id	500
the	O
song	O
also	O
appears	O
in	O
the	B-CW
hangover	I-CW
part	I-CW
iii	I-CW
,	O
directed	O
by	O
todd	B-PER
phillips	I-PER
.	O

#	id	504
also	O
honda	B-PROD
city	I-PROD
cars	O
were	O
more	O
reliable	O
and	O
suspension	O
tuning	O
became	O
the	O
deciding	O
factor	O
for	O
vehicle	O
performance	O
.	O

#	id	506
what	O
does	O
redhill	B-LOC
station	I-LOC
measure	O

#	id	507
since	O
2002	O
,	O
the	O
team	O
welcomed	O
hiromi	B-PER
hara	I-PER
as	O
its	O
manager	O
and	O
aimed	O
for	O
a	O
championship	O
with	O
a	O
strong	O
offense	O
.	O

#	id	509
canyon	O
was	O
a	O
bay	O
mare	O
bred	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
edward	B-PER
stanley,	I-PER
17th	I-PER
earl	I-PER
of	I-PER
derby	I-PER
.	O

#	id	510
mojo	B-CW
magazine	O
ranked	O
it	O
29th	O
on	O
its	O
list	O
of	O
2001	O
's	O
best	O
records	O
.	O

#	id	512
in	O
943	O
wang	B-PER
yanzheng	I-PER
revolted	O
and	O
formed	O
yin	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	513
it	O
is	O
listed	O
as	O
threatened	O
in	O
connecticut	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
as	O
a	O
species	O
of	O
special	O
concern	O
in	O
massachusetts	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	514
he	O
has	O
played	O
in	O
major	B-CORP
league	I-CORP
baseball	I-CORP
(	O
mlb	O
)	O
with	O
the	O
washington	B-GRP
nationals	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	515
utopia	B-CW
was	O
released	O
in	O
1982	O
for	O
the	O
intellivision	B-PROD
,	O
and	O
is	O
credited	O
as	O
the	O
game	O
that	O
spawned	O
the	O
construction	O
and	O
management	O
simulation	O
genre	O
.	O

#	id	517
dry	B-GRP
dock	I-GRP
:	O
a	O
narrow	O
basin	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
flooded	O
and	O
drained	O
to	O
allow	O
a	O
load	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
rest	O
on	O
a	O
dry	O
platform	O

#	id	518
the	O
cartoon	O
is	O
loosely	O
based	O
on	O
the	O
capcom	B-CORP
fighting	O
game	O
darkstalkers:	B-CW
the	I-CW
night	I-CW
warriors	I-CW
.	O

#	id	519
pathapatnam	O
is	O
located	O
on	O
the	O
banks	O
of	O
mahendratanaya	B-LOC
river	I-LOC

#	id	520
it	O
is	O
51.2	O
km	O
long	O
and	O
connects	O
state	B-LOC
highway	I-LOC
6	I-LOC
with	O
the	O
settlement	O
of	O
mokihinui	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	523
hunter	O
had	O
a	O
major	O
role	O
in	O
the	O
1988	O
horror	B-CW
film	I-CW
cameron's	B-CW
closet	I-CW
.	O

#	id	524
he	O
failed	O
to	O
attract	O
much	O
attention	O
at	O
the	O
sale	O
due	O
to	O
a	O
problem	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
feet	O
,	O
since	O
corrected	O
by	O
horseshoe	B-PROD
.	O

#	id	526
his	O
playlist	O
includes	O
sonny	B-PER
sharrock	I-PER
,	O
gza	B-PER
,	O
country	B-GRP
teasers	I-GRP
and	O
the	B-PER
notorious	I-PER
b.i.g.	I-PER

#	id	527
thompson	O
was	O
educated	O
at	O
cheltenham	B-GRP
college	I-GRP
and	O
then	O
attended	O
the	O
royal	B-GRP
military	I-GRP
academy	I-GRP
before	O
being	O
commissioned	O
into	O
the	O
royal	B-GRP
artillery	I-GRP
in	O
1929	O
.	O

#	id	528
they	O
play	O
in	O
the	O
south	B-GRP
of	I-GRP
scotland	I-GRP
football	I-GRP
league	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	529
in	O
fact	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
introduction	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
second	O
largest	O
fighter	O
engine	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
length	O
of	O
6.1	O
m	O
and	O
1.35	O
m	O
diameter	O
;	O
only	O
the	O
tumansky	B-PROD
r-15	I-PROD
was	O
bigger	O
.	O

#	id	530
the	O
original	O
complex	O
included	O
two	O
supermarkets	O
and	O
two	O
variety	O
stores	O
,	O
plus	O
a	O
belk	B-CORP
department	O
store	O
.	O

#	id	531
this	O
nonprofit	O
organization	O
is	O
located	O
across	O
the	O
united	B-LOC
states	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
america	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	532
the	O
tiger	O
's	O
full	O
genome	B-PROD
sequence	O
was	O
published	O
in	O
2013	O
.	O

#	id	533
makes	B-CW
me	I-CW
wonder	I-CW
(	O
levine	O
,	O
jesse	B-PER
carmichael	I-PER
and	O
mickey	B-PER
madden	I-PER
)	O
–	O
4	O
:	O
36	O

#	id	534
it	O
was	O
originally	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
london	B-CORP
and	I-CORP
blackwall	I-CORP
railway	I-CORP
and	O
had	O
one	O
intermediate	O
station	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
today	O
,	O
no	O
regular	O
timetabled	O
services	O
run	O
on	O
this	O
line	O
.	O

#	id	535
the	O
district	O
hosts	O
the	O
headquarters	O
of	O
military	O
region	O
in	O
the	O
province	O
and	O
is	O
also	O
known	O
for	O
its	O
prison	O
where	O
political	O
prisoners	O
such	O
as	O
zhu	B-PER
yufu	I-PER
are	O
incarcerated	O
.	O

#	id	536
a	O
sequel	O
,	O
shadow	B-CW
hearts:	I-CW
covenant	I-CW
,	O
was	O
released	O
in	O
2004	O
.	O

#	id	537
it	O
is	O
found	O
on	O
madagascar	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	538
whole	O
durian	B-PROD
(	O
allowed	O
sliced	O
,	O
dried	O
or	O
packed	O
durian	O
)	O
,	O
coconuts	O
and	O
watermelons	O
.	O

#	id	539
the	B-CW
nine	I-CW
chapters	I-CW
on	I-CW
the	I-CW
mathematical	I-CW
art	I-CW
had	O
used	O
the	O
value	O
3	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
zhang	B-PER
heng	I-PER
(	O
78	O
139	O
ad	O
)	O
had	O
previously	O
estimated	O
pi	O
to	O
the	O
square	O
root	O
of	O
10	O
.	O

#	id	541
skitching	O
is	O
also	O
possible	O
in	O
skate	B-CW
2	I-CW
.	O

#	id	542
,	O
2011	O
,	O
published	O
by	O
shogakukan	B-CORP
.	O

#	id	543
pittsford	O
is	O
the	O
home	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
largest	O
wegmans	B-CORP
stores	O
in	O
the	O
state	O
.	O

#	id	544
subsequently	O
,	O
the	O
station	O
served	O
passengers	O
on	O
the	O
pennsylvania-reading	B-GRP
seashore	I-GRP
lines	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	545
the	O
most	O
renowned	O
scholar	O
monk	O
based	O
in	O
the	O
abbey	O
was	O
adelard	B-PER
of	I-PER
bath	I-PER
;	O
after	O
his	O
various	O
travels	O
he	O
was	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
monastery	O
by	O
1106	O
.	O

#	id	546
the	B-CW
breeze	I-CW
and	I-CW
i	I-CW
(	O
ernesto	B-PER
lecuona	I-PER
,	O
al	B-PER
stillman	I-PER
)	O
6	O
:	O
51	O

#	id	547
lyrics	B-CW
typically	O
center	O
on	O
love	O
,	O
relationships	O
,	O
and	O
feelings	O
.	O

#	id	548
he	O
is	O
also	O
famous	O
for	O
his	O
recorded	B-CW
history	I-CW
of	O
the	O
mongol	B-LOC
empire	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	551
she	O
is	O
married	O
to	O
harish	B-PER
khare	I-PER
.	O

#	id	552
it	O
was	O
also	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
bbc	B-CORP
two	I-CORP
series	O
top	B-CW
gear	I-CW
in	O
episode	O
4	O
of	O
series	O
21	O
.	O

#	id	553
interference	O
based	O
coatings	O
were	O
invented	O
and	O
developed	O
in	O
1935	O
by	O
olexander	B-PER
smakula	I-PER
,	O
who	O
was	O
working	O
for	O
the	O
carl	B-CORP
zeiss	I-CORP
ag	I-CORP
optics	O
company	O
.	O

#	id	554
a	O
professional	O
from	O
2006	O
until	O
2014	O
,	O
he	O
also	O
competed	O
for	O
strikeforce	B-CORP
.	O

#	id	555
the	O
family	O
moved	O
to	O
glendale	B-LOC
,	O
california	B-LOC
when	O
the	O
brothers	O
were	O
young	O
.	O

#	id	556
mccall	O
worked	O
at	O
mcdonald’s	B-CORP
to	O
pay	O
her	O
tuition	O
.	O

#	id	557
he	O
also	O
recorded	O
several	O
albums	O
and	O
participated	O
to	O
several	O
editions	O
of	O
the	O
sanremo	B-CW
music	I-CW
festival	I-CW
as	O
a	O
singer	O
.	O

#	id	558
danielle	B-PER
robinson	I-PER
(	O
2011	O
–	O
2016	O
)	O
,	O
now	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
minnesota	B-GRP
lynx	I-GRP

#	id	560
the	O
ceramic	B-PROD
sector	O
is	O
concentrated	O
in	O
faenza	B-LOC
and	O
sassuolo	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	561
he	O
previously	O
played	O
as	O
a	O
or	O
for	O
the	O
newcastle	B-GRP
knights	I-GRP
,	O
parramatta	B-GRP
eels	I-GRP
,	O
wests	B-GRP
tigers	I-GRP
and	O
the	O
cronulla-sutherland	B-GRP
sharks	I-GRP
in	O
the	O
national	B-GRP
rugby	I-GRP
league	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	562
optional	O
ntfs	B-CW
hard	O
and	O
symbolic	O
links	O
.	O

#	id	563
a	O
new	O
holiday	B-CORP
inn	I-CORP
hotel	O
complex	O
was	O
constructed	O
in	O
1998	O
between	O
8th	O
and	O
9th	O
streets	O
.	O

#	id	564
he	O
became	O
interested	O
in	O
music	O
at	O
a	O
very	O
young	O
age	O
and	O
was	O
encouraged	O
by	O
mohamed	O
k	O
hioudji	O
,	O
hadj	B-PER
m'rizek	I-PER
half	O
brother	O
.	O

#	id	565
written	O
to	O
be	O
performed	O
without	O
intermission	O
,	O
the	O
musical	O
combines	O
episodes	O
from	O
the	O
novel	O
with	O
a	O
story	O
about	O
miguel	B-PER
de	I-PER
cervantes	I-PER
,	O
as	O
a	O
play	O
within	O
a	O
play	O
.	O

#	id	566
heartlight	B-CW
,	O
1982	O
;	O
primitive	B-CW
,	O
1984	O
;	O
headed	B-CW
for	I-CW
the	I-CW
future	I-CW
,	O
1986	O
.	O

#	id	567
instead	O
,	O
they	O
decided	O
to	O
ship	O
hydrogen	O
in	O
insulated	O
tanks	O
on	O
the	O
florida	B-LOC
state	I-LOC
road	I-LOC
710	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	568
yesss	O
,	O
a	O
character	O
in	O
the	O
animated	O
film	O
ralph	B-CW
breaks	I-CW
the	I-CW
internet	I-CW

#	id	569
both	O
these	O
formations	O
have	O
yielded	O
stone	B-PROD
tool	I-PROD
.	O

#	id	570
8	O
.	O

#	id	571
it	O
is	O
hunted	O
as	O
bushmeat	B-PROD
.	O

#	id	572
his	O
second	O
directorial	O
feature	O
,	O
the	B-CW
postman	I-CW
,	O
was	O
released	O
in	O
1997	O
.	O

#	id	573
bettys	B-CORP
and	I-CORP
taylors	I-CORP
of	I-CORP
harrogate	I-CORP
,	O
traditional	O
tea	O
rooms	O
dating	O
from	O
1919	O
.	O

#	id	574
between	O
1878	O
and	O
1885	O
he	O
cooperated	O
with	O
henrik	B-PER
nissen	I-PER
.	O

#	id	575
franco	B-PER
ferreiro	I-PER
/	O
andré	B-PER
sá	I-PER
def	O
.	O
santiago	B-PER
gonzález	I-PER
/	O
horacio	B-PER
zeballos	I-PER
,	O
7	O
–	O
5	O
,	O
7	O
–	O
6	O

#	id	576
the	O
main	O
contractor	O
was	O
ssangyong	B-CORP
engineering	I-CORP
and	I-CORP
construction	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	578
turbulence	B-CW
(	O
laidback	B-PER
luke	I-PER
and	O
steve	B-PER
aoki	I-PER
featuring	O
lil	O
jon	O
)	O

#	id	579
lost	O
to	O
eventual	O
champion	O
matsushita	B-GRP
denko	I-GRP
impulse	I-GRP
45	O
17	O
.	O

#	id	580
his	O
favourite	O
grip	O
on	O
his	O
opponent	O
's	O
mawashi	B-PROD
was	O
hidari	O
yotsu	O
,	O
a	O
right	O
hand	O
outside	O
,	O
left	O
hand	O
inside	O
position	O
.	O

#	id	581
wawel	O
is	O
a	O
poland	B-LOC
confection	B-PROD
company	O
,	O
producing	O
many	O
varieties	O
of	O
chocolate	B-PROD
,	O
wafers	O
,	O
chocolate	O
bars	O
and	O
snacks	O
.	O

#	id	582
quadratus	B-PER
of	I-PER
athens	I-PER
(	O
2nd	O
century	O
,	O
sometimes	O
considered	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
seventy	O
apostles	O
)	O

#	id	583
he	O
is	O
currently	O
under	O
a	O
contract	O
with	O
tvb	B-CORP
.	O

#	id	585
the	O
mini	O
album	O
art	B-CW
of	I-CW
life	I-CW
was	O
released	O
in	O
1993	O
,	O
composed	O
solely	O
of	O
the	O
29	O
minute	O
title	O
track	O
.	O

#	id	586
most	O
of	O
the	O
collection	O
is	O
from	O
1881	O
to	O
1914	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
relevant	O
to	O
the	O
history	O
of	O
the	O
pittsburgh	B-LOC
region	O
.	O

#	id	587
most	O
passing	O
yards	O
,	O
rookie	O
season	O
:	O
russell	B-PER
wilson	I-PER
,	O
3,118	O

#	id	588
shane	B-PER
battier	I-PER
of	O
duke	B-GRP
blue	I-GRP
devils	I-GRP
men's	I-GRP
basketball	I-GRP
was	O
the	O
leading	O
vote	O
getter	O
(	O
71	O
of	O
72	O
votes	O
)	O
.	O

#	id	589
silvio	B-PER
spann	I-PER
–	O
(	O
cro	O
)	O
–	O
gnk	B-GRP
dinamo	I-GRP
zagreb	I-GRP
2003	O
–	O
2005	O

#	id	590
1537	O
1543	O
:	O
claude	B-PER
de	I-PER
rohan-gié	I-PER
(	O
fille	O
d	O
honneur	O
de	O
1530	O
à	O
1537	O
)	O

#	id	591
the	O
main	O
cash	O
crop	O
is	O
coffee	B-PROD
.	O

#	id	592
a	O
nail	O
bomb	O
is	O
also	O
a	O
type	O
of	O
flechette	B-PROD
weapon	O
.	O

#	id	593
couscous	B-PROD
,	O
rice	O
and	O
bean	B-PROD
are	O
also	O
commonly	O
eaten	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
fruits	O
such	O
as	O
mango	B-PROD
,	O
oranges	O
,	O
and	O
avocados	O
.	O

#	id	595
the	O
series	O
also	O
produced	O
spin	O
off	O
titles	O
including	O
saga	B-CW
and	O
mana	B-CW
,	O
and	O
in	O
turn	O
influenced	O
later	O
game	O
developers	O
and	O
studios	O
.	O

#	id	596
he	O
was	O
consequently	O
noted	O
by	O
newly	O
promoted	O
serie	B-GRP
a	I-GRP
club	O
a.c.	B-GRP
pisa	I-GRP
1909	I-GRP
,	O
who	O
signed	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
2007	O
–	O
2008	O
season	O
.	O

#	id	597
it	O
was	O
originally	O
published	O
by	O
little,	B-CORP
brown	I-CORP
and	I-CORP
company	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	598
a	O
jockstrap	O
is	O
different	O
from	O
a	O
dance	B-PROD
belt	I-PROD
that	O
a	O
male	O
dancer	O
wears	O
.	O

#	id	599
many	O
technology	O
companies	O
invested	O
in	O
the	O
consumer	O
electronics	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
technology	O
,	O
including	O
intel	B-CORP
,	O
qualcomm	B-CORP
inc.	I-CORP
,	O
samsung	B-CORP
electronics	I-CORP
and	O
others	O
.	O

#	id	600
in	O
2000	O
monica	B-PER
recorded	O
a	O
version	O
that	O
was	O
released	O
on	O
the	O
platinum	B-CW
christmas	I-CW
various	O
artists	O
compilation	O
album	O
.	O

#	id	601
ne	O
of	O
livonia	B-LOC
(	O
2nd	O
tornado	O
)	O

#	id	602
thomas	O
served	O
as	O
co-operative	B-GRP
party	I-GRP
from	O
2001	O
until	O
2019	O
.	O

#	id	604
a	O
later	O
expansion	O
added	O
a	O
new	O
wing	O
and	O
dillard's	B-CORP
store	O
to	O
the	O
center	O
after	O
westfield	B-CORP
group	I-CORP
purchased	O
the	O
mall	O
.	O

#	id	605
it	O
was	O
also	O
arranged	O
for	O
the	O
royal	B-CORP
philharmonic	I-CORP
orchestra	I-CORP
for	O
the	O
2015	O
compilation	O
album	O
,	O
if	B-CW
i	I-CW
can	I-CW
dream	I-CW
.	O

#	id	607
this	O
forced	O
the	O
christian	B-GRP
social	I-GRP
union	I-GRP
of	I-GRP
bavaria	I-GRP
(	O
csu	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
power	O
for	O
three	O
years	O
.	O

#	id	608
quintet	O
,	O
with	O
charles	B-PER
mcpherson	I-PER
(	O
alto	O
sax	O
)	O
,	O
sam	B-PER
noto	I-PER
(	O
trumpet	O
)	O
,	O
leroy	B-PER
vinnegar	I-PER
(	O
bass	O
)	O
,	O
frank	B-PER
butler	I-PER
(	O
drums	O
)	O

#	id	609
one	O
of	O
his	O
classmates	O
was	O
jack	B-PER
johnson	I-PER
.	O

#	id	610
in	O
1899	O
he	O
moved	O
to	O
brno	B-LOC
,	O
where	O
he	O
designed	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
and	O
a	O
new	O
lodging	O
house	O
for	O
the	O
local	O
school	O
.	O

#	id	611
podhradie	O
is	O
a	O
village	B-LOC
and	O
municipality	B-LOC
in	O
martin	B-LOC
district	I-LOC
in	O
the	O
žilina	B-LOC
region	I-LOC
of	O
northern	O
slovakia	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	612
it	O
has	O
many	O
historical	O
carvings	O
and	O
boards	O
inscribed	O
with	O
calligraphy	B-CW
from	O
famous	O
people	O
.	O

#	id	613
that	B-CW
touch	I-CW
of	I-CW
mink	I-CW
–	O
writer	O
,	O
producer	O

#	id	615
the	O
films	O
featured	O
former	O
footballer	O
and	O
commentator	O
robbie	B-PER
savage	I-PER
and	O
countdown	B-CW
co	O
host	O
rachel	B-PER
riley	I-PER
among	O
others	O
.	O

#	id	616
in	O
1969	O
he	O
graduated	O
from	O
harvard	B-GRP
law	I-GRP
school	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	617
for	O
example	O
,	O
many	O
believe	O
that	O
blood	B-PROD
is	O
not	O
replenished	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
therefore	O
reluctant	O
to	O
have	O
their	O
blood	O
drawn	O
.	O

#	id	618
the	O
object	O
is	O
a	O
single	O
piece	O
of	O
whelk	B-PROD
shell	O
that	O
has	O
an	O
engraving	O
of	O
a	O
mammoth	O
on	O
one	O
surface	O
while	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
is	O
undecorated	O
.	O

#	id	619
carried	O
railway	O
over	O
the	O
river	B-LOC
parrett	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	620
how	O
much	O
is	O
adrian	B-PER
lam	I-PER
worth	O

#	id	621
the	O
song	O
was	O
included	O
on	O
the	O
group	O
's	O
1972	O
self	O
titled	O
album	O
on	O
atlantic	B-CORP
records	I-CORP
,	O
their	O
first	O
album	O
release	O
for	O
the	O
label	O
.	O

#	id	622
a	O
statue	O
of	O
benjamin	B-PER
franklin	I-PER
was	O
displayed	O
at	O
the	O
entrance	O
.	O

#	id	623
it	O
follows	O
the	O
plot	O
of	O
the	O
animated	O
film	O
the	B-CW
lego	I-CW
movie	I-CW
.	O

#	id	624
he	O
eventually	O
ended	O
up	O
in	O
texas	B-LOC
and	O
allegedly	O
joined	O
the	O
texas	B-GRP
ranger	I-GRP
division	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	625
jwpce	O
can	O
also	O
display	O
kanji	O
in	O
a	O
list	O
you	O
generate	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
color	B-PROD
so	O
that	O
it	O
colors	O
either	O
the	O
kanji	O
that	O
the	O
user	O
does	O
not	O
know	O
or	O
that	O
the	O
user	O
does	O
know	O
.	O

#	id	626
she	O
has	O
been	O
trained	O
in	O
kuchipudi	B-CW
dance	O
and	O
singing	O
from	O
childhood	O
.	O

#	id	627
in	O
2015	O
the	O
team	O
switched	O
from	O
ktm	B-CORP
to	O
husqvarna	B-CORP
motorcycles	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	628
the	O
northern	B-GRP
counties	I-GRP
committee	I-GRP
(	O
and	O
the	O
ballycastle	O
railway	O
)	O
was	O
thus	O
briefly	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
british	B-GRP
transport	I-GRP
commission	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	629
he	O
remained	O
a	O
member	O
through	O
the	O
series	O
cancellation	O
with	O
issue	O
25	O
(	O
april	O
2010	O
)	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
team	O
disbanded	O
after	O
the	B-CW
thanos	I-CW
imperative	I-CW
(	O
dec	O
2010	O
)	O
.	O

#	id	631
it	O
ran	O
from	O
1988	O
to	O
1994	O
on	O
tv	B-CORP
asahi	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	632
from	O
1961	O
he	O
served	O
the	O
royal	B-GRP
norwegian	I-GRP
army	I-GRP
in	O
kirkenes	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	633
anand	O
writes	O
columns	O
for	O
mainstream	O
newspapers	O
such	O
as	O
the	B-GRP
indian	I-GRP
express	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	634
cox	O
moved	O
to	O
los	B-LOC
angeles	I-LOC
and	O
eventually	O
found	O
herself	O
struggling	O
with	O
social	O
media	O
addiction	O
and	O
online	O
persona	O
.	O

#	id	635
during	O
his	O
period	O
,	O
she	O
became	O
an	O
active	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
democratic	B-GRP
party	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	636
about	O
22	O
million	O
women	O
and	O
5.5	O
million	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
european	B-GRP
union	I-GRP
had	O
osteoporosis	O
in	O
2010	O
.	O

#	id	637
westwood	O
worked	O
closely	O
with	O
richard	B-PER
branson	I-PER
to	O
design	O
uniforms	O
for	O
virgin	B-CORP
atlantic	I-CORP
crew	O
.	O

#	id	638
playstation	B-PROD
3	I-PROD
,	O
playstation	B-CW
vita	I-CW
,	O
playstation	B-PROD
4	I-PROD
,	O
xbox	B-PROD
one	I-PROD
,	O
wii	B-PROD
u	I-PROD
,	O
microsoft	B-CW
windows	I-CW

#	id	639
polygyros	O
is	O
famous	O
for	O
its	O
carnival	B-GRP
celebrations	O
,	O
which	O
attracts	O
visitors	O
from	O
all	O
over	O
greece	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	640
as	O
result	O
the	O
game	O
was	O
ported	O
by	O
the	O
game	O
's	O
community	O
to	O
alternative	O
platforms	O
like	O
the	O
pandora	B-CW
handheld	O
.	O

#	id	641
ivory	B-LOC
coast	I-LOC
:	O
yamoussoukro	B-LOC
was	O
designated	O
the	O
national	O
capital	O
in	O
1983	O
,	O
but	O
most	O
government	O
offices	O
and	O
embassies	O
are	O
still	O
located	O
in	O
abidjan	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	642
bar	O
:	O
2	O
color	O
:	O
tan2	O
from	O
:	O
1970	O
till	O
:	O
end	O
text	O
:	O
pbs	B-CORP

#	id	643
it	O
is	O
4	O
km	O
northwest	O
of	O
zakynthos	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	644
alinda	O
appears	O
on	O
byzantine	B-LOC
empire	I-LOC
lists	O
of	O
bishoprics	O
.	O

#	id	645
he	O
was	O
unable	O
to	O
capture	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
encouraged	O
the	O
infidel	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
contemporary	O
jacques	B-PER
de	I-PER
vitry	I-PER
.	O

#	id	646
he	O
also	O
remains	O
a	O
director	O
of	O
tribune	B-CORP
publishing	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	647
the	B-CW
pianist	I-CW
–	O
ronald	B-PER
harwood	I-PER
based	O
on	O
the	B-CW
pianist	I-CW
by	O
władysław	B-PER
szpilman	I-PER

#	id	648
the	O
film	O
was	O
directed	O
by	O
maria	B-PER
mochnacz	I-PER
and	O
released	O
only	O
on	O
dvd	B-PROD
.	O

#	id	649
originally	O
composed	O
for	O
a	O
bbc	B-CORP
radio	I-CORP
3	I-CORP
documentary	O
.	O

#	id	650
engaged	O
in	O
escorting	O
trains	O
and	O
u.s.	O
mail	O
coaches	O
on	O
the	O
santa	B-LOC
fe	I-LOC
trail	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	651
she	O
appeared	O
at	O
linz	B-LOC
in	O
1954	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
also	O
early	O
appearances	O
at	O
the	O
carltheater	B-LOC
in	O
vienna	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	652
in	O
kirkus	B-CW
reviews	I-CW
it	O
was	O
praised	O
as	O
a	O
fascinating	O
,	O
vigorously	O
argued	O
work	O
that	O
probes	O
deeply	O
into	O
the	O
way	O
“	O
weird	O
people	O
”	O
think	O
.	O

#	id	653
bern	B-PER
porter	I-PER
(	O
1911	O
2004	O
)	O
,	O
artist	O
,	O
writer	O
,	O
and	O
scientist	O

#	id	654
in	O
1962	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
given	O
an	O
eighteen	O
month	O
prison	O
term	O
for	O
selling	O
honey	B-PROD
under	O
false	O
pretences	O
.	O

#	id	655
cholpon-ata	B-LOC
airport	I-LOC
and	O
tamga	B-LOC
airport	I-LOC
have	O
no	O
regular	O
flights	O
.	O

#	id	656
he	O
was	O
bass	O
player	O
in	O
the	O
band	O
echo	B-GRP
&	I-GRP
the	I-GRP
bunnymen	I-GRP
from	O
2000	O
to	O
2001	O
.	O

#	id	657
for	O
example	O
,	O
the	O
1922	O
film	O
sherlock	B-CW
holmes	I-CW
was	O
eventually	O
discovered	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
footage	O
is	O
still	O
missing	O
.	O

#	id	659
the	O
locomotives	O
were	O
used	O
on	O
the	O
electrified	O
portion	O
of	O
the	O
railroad	O
,	O
from	O
wenatchee	B-LOC
to	O
skykomish	B-LOC
,	O
including	O
the	O
cascade	B-LOC
tunnel	I-LOC
.	O

#	id	660
since	O
1993	O
,	O
the	O
festivities	O
have	O
been	O
held	O
in	O
pontivy	B-LOC
(	O
morbihan	B-LOC
)	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
1997	O
it	O
was	O
passed	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
its	O
eponym	O
.	O

#	id	662
lostprophets	O
were	O
signed	O
to	O
columbia	B-CORP
records	I-CORP
and	O
visible	B-CORP
noise	I-CORP
in	O
2000	O
and	O
released	O
5	O
studio	O
albums	O
before	O
dissolving	O
.	O

#	id	663
his	O
recordings	O
include	O
several	O
issues	O
for	O
hyperion	B-CORP
records	I-CORP
,	O
including	O
music	O
of	O
benjamin	B-PER
britten	I-PER
,	O
emmanuel	B-PER
chabrier	I-PER
,	O
maurice	B-PER
duruflé	I-PER
and	O
henry	B-PER
purcell	I-PER
.	O

#	id	664
they	O
also	O
lost	O
the	O
bronze	O
medal	O
match	O
against	O
simon	B-PER
archer	I-PER
and	O
joanne	B-PER
goode	I-PER
of	O
great	B-LOC
britain	I-LOC
15	O
4	O
,	O
12	O
15	O
,	O
17	O
14	O
.	O

#	id	665
stephens	O
began	O
his	O
career	O
as	O
a	O
poet	O
under	O
the	O
tutelage	O
of	O
poet	O
and	O
painter	O
æ	O
(	O
george	B-PER
william	I-PER
russell	I-PER
)	O
.	O

#	id	666
mulcahy	O
was	O
the	O
original	O
director	O
on	O
rambo	B-CW
iii	I-CW
.	O

#	id	667
it	O
is	O
a	O
dual	O
purpose	O
breed	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
raised	O
principally	O
for	O
milk	B-PROD
production	O
.	O

#	id	668
in	O
1974	O
he	O
graduated	O
from	O
law	O
school	O
at	O
parahyangan	B-GRP
catholic	I-GRP
university	I-GRP
in	O
bandung	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	669
the	O
film	O
series	O
has	O
since	O
been	O
rebooted	O
with	O
a	O
lethal	B-CW
weapon	I-CW
,	O
currently	O
airing	O
on	O
fox	B-CORP
broadcasting	I-CORP
company	I-CORP
.	O

#	id	670
elsewhen	B-CW
,	O
1941	O
(	O
a.k.a.	O
elsewhere	O
)	O
(	O
as	O
caleb	O
saunders	O
)	O

#	id	672
franziska	B-PER
weber	I-PER
and	O
tina	B-PER
dietze	I-PER
,	O
representing	O
germany	B-GRP
at	I-GRP
the	I-GRP
2012	I-GRP
summer	I-GRP
olympics	I-GRP
,	O
won	O
the	O
gold	O
medal	O
.	O

#	id	674
she	O
defeated	O
jessica	B-PER
moore	I-PER
and	O
alexandra	B-PER
panova	I-PER
but	O
was	O
defeated	O
by	O
anastasia	B-PER
pivovarova	I-PER
in	O
the	O
third	O
qualifying	O
round	O
.	O

#	id	675
salifou	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
zinder	B-LOC
.	O

#	id	676
schadlow	O
is	O
a	O
full	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
council	B-GRP
on	I-GRP
foreign	I-GRP
relations	I-GRP
.	O

#	id	677
computer	B-PROD
hardware	I-PROD
:	O
the	O
hardware	O
needed	O
to	O
access	O
the	O
digital	O
file	O
becomes	O
obsolete	O
and	O
thus	O
no	O
longer	O
available	O
.	O

#	id	678
finally	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
also	O
synced	O
to	O
an	O
iphone	B-PROD
app	O
which	O
allows	O
for	O
tracking	O
and	O
sharing	O
of	O
personal	O
record	O
and	O
achievements	O
.	O

#	id	679
cfg	O
joined	O
the	O
newly	O
created	O
ig	B-CORP
farben	I-CORP
as	O
an	O
associate	O
company	O
in	O
1916	O
.	O

#	id	680
foster	O
is	O
also	O
credited	O
with	O
composing	O
grown-up	B-CW
christmas	I-CW
list	I-CW
.	O
